here we
here we
go the fin here perform it for you if
go the fin here perform it for you if
you know the words you can join him to
you know the words you can join him to
put your hands together if
put your hands Together if
you as we take you through this Monkey
you as we take you through this Monkey
[Music]
[Música]
Kong Donkey Kong He's the leader of the
Kong Donkey Kong He's the leader of the
bunch you know him well He's Finally
bunch you know him well He's Finally
back to Kick some Coconut
back to Kick some Coconut
gum and If he shoots It's gna hur He's
gum and If he shoots It's gna hur He's
bigger faster and stronger to He's the
bigger faster and stronger to He's the
First member of the d
First member of the d
Crew Donkey
Crew Donkey
Kong Donkey
Kong Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is here
Kong Donkey Kong is here
Donkey
Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong
Kong Donkey Kong
is got
is got
link
link
si her
si her
and When She needs to be She can float
and When She needs to be She can float
through the air and Climb up Tree if you
through the air and Climb up Tree if you
choose
choose
her wrong with the sk a H She's
her wrong with the sk a H She's
cool Donkey
cool Donkey
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Kong Donkey Kong is
Kong Donkey Kong is
here Donkey
here Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is no Style he has no
Kong Donkey Kong is no Style he has no
Grace this Kong has a funny Face he can hand
Grace this Kong has a funny Face he can
when he needs to and stretch his
hand when he needs to and stretch his
Arms out Just for you inflate himself
Arms out Just for you inflate himself
just like a balloon this Crazy Just digs
just like a balloon this Crazy Just digs
his
his
[Music]
[Música]
tunke Kong is
tunke Kong is
Donkey
Donkey
Kong  Donkey Kong is herey
Kong Donkey Kong is herey
[Music]
[Música]
donke
donke
kke Kong He's Back Again and about to
kke Kong He's Back Again and about to
and this Time He's in the mo he can F
and this Time He's in the mo he can F
real H with Jet with his pistols out
real H with Jet with his pistols out
He's One tough he'll Make You Smile when
He's One tough he'll Make You Smile when
he Plays his Tun but bew Kong
he Plays his Tun but bew
Donkey Kong is
Kong Donkey Kong is
here Donkey
here Donkey
Kong Kong is Finally He's here for you
Kong Kong is Finally He's here for you
It's The Last member of the dk Crew this
It's The Last member of the dk Crew this
K so strong it isn't funny can makein
K so strong it isn't funny can makein
Cry out
Cry out
fory pick up a with  eas makes crushing
fory pick up a with eas makes crushing
Rocks seem such a breeze he May move Slow he can't jump High but this Hell Of A Come on cranky take it to the fridge
Rocks seem such a breeze he May move
pineapple
oh yeah walnuts peut pineapple
smell Coconut
smell Coconut
good How are you how are you
bueno Qué tal estáis qué tal estáis
family I always like to stop by
familia me me gusta siempre pasarme por
here on Thursdays whether or not there is much
aquí los jueves haya o no haya mucho
topic because already  you know that I usually
tema porque ya sabéis que suelo
disappear or I try to I don't try to
desaparecer o lo intento no intento
disappear on the weekends at
desaparecer los fines de semana por lo
least Friday Saturday I usually disappear
menos viernes sábado suelo desaparecer
no and well if I do connect it's a little bit or
no y y bueno si me conecto es poquillo o
some videos that are scheduled on
algunos vídeos que estén programados en
the main channel I don't promise anything I don't promise
el canal principal no prometo nada no
anything but maybe the day after
prometo nada pero capaz que ya pasado
tomorrow or on Sunday
mañana o el domingo se vuelva a estrenar
the rewind will be released again with some arrangements okay we already
el rewind con algunos arreglos vale ya
have more or less
tenemos más o menos
eh the notes I didn't do it ales of
eh los apuntes no me lo hizo ales de las
things to improve Okay and to square them I
cosas a mejorar Vale y a cuadrar yo les
want to take a look at them to see if I can
quiero pegar un repasito para ver si
change the order of some things and
cambiar el orden de algunas cosas e
even summarize another one maybe I don't know what
incluso resumir otra igual no sé qué
music to put replacing Ricky's thing I have
música poner sustituyendo lo de Ricky
n't thought about it yet I don't know what
todavía no lo he pensado no sé qué que
another song could be good there not
otra canción pudiera quedar bien ahí no
that talks about love heartbreak and and
que que hable de de amor desamor y y
all those things no and that has to do
todas esas cosas no y que tenga que ver
with streamer or I mean it would be it would be
con con streamer o sea es que sería
great but right now I don't know what I don't
sería genial pero ahora mismo no sé qué
know if maybe some I don't know if I
no sé si a lo mejor alguna no sé si
could take maybe and ask
podría [__] a lo mejor y pedirle
marlucas for permission Maybe to
permiso a marlucas A lo mejor para para
put hers or something like that I don't know the
poner la suya o algo así no lo sé la
truth but I don't know if it's a delicate enough subject
verdad pero no sé si es un tema bastante
to put it there I don't know
delicado como para ponerlo ahí No lo sé
the truth is I have to see it okay e But
la verdad lo tengo que ver vale e Pero
well, normally I usually retire on
bueno normalmente suelo retirarme
Friday and Saturday, on Saturday I have
viernes y sábado el sábado tengo planes
family plans, normally on Sunday I usually
familiares normalmente el domingo suelo
take the child to see animals
llevar al niño a ver animales a
anywhere whatever
cualquier sitio lo que sea
and and well although there isn't much today, we are
y y bueno aunque no hay mucha cosa hoy
going to comment on some okay
sí que vamos a comentar algunas vale
also I'll tell you tomorrow Today I have to
también te digo mañana Hoy tengo que
spend the night, probably awake No, I don't
pasar la noche seguramente despierto No
want to stay here very late eh No, you're
no me quiero quedar aquí muy tarde eh No
not going to confuse me too much because I have to
no me vais a enrollar mucho porque tengo
prepare the podcast that is recorded
que preparar el podcast que se graba
tomorrow and for the ía to do it for you Well it
mañana y que te la haga la ía Pues
's also true no in
también es verdad no em
the podcast tomorrow I record the podcast
el podcast mañana lo grabo el podcast
with Dani Estévez desocupa and Fran cuesta
con Dani Estévez desocupa y Fran cuesta
So I have, I have to spend the
Así que tengo tengo tengo que pasar la
night probably working so I don't
noche seguramente trabajando así que no
want to leave here very late it's
me quiero ir de aquí muy tarde son las
1 I hope no more than an hour I hope no
1 Espero no más de una hora Espero no
more than an hour
más de una hora
Okay what can I tell you, well
Vale qué os digo pues que
last night I really discovered something that
anoche de verdad descubrí una cosa que
for those of you who are old on the channel I
para los que seáis antiguos en el canal
mean for those of you who have been here for
O sea para los que lleváis aquí Ya por
at least 5co 6 7 years
lo menos 5co 6 7 años
or You're going to get it very quickly no because it
o Vais a pillarla rapidísimo no porque
has its lores But the truth is that it has
tiene su lores Pero la verdad es que me
surprised me quite a bit It turns out to
ha me ha sorprendido bastante No resulta
be that Well to  my Pablo had
ser que Bueno a mí Pablo me había
told me at some point okay in this
comentado en algún momento vale en esta
that he was litigating with him with the guy
que estaba litigando con el con el chico
this laser len had told me at
este laser len me había comentado en
some point that the lawyer had been
algún momento que la abogada se había
messing with him on Twitter okay
estado metiendo con él por Twitter vale
at some point I made some comment like let's
en algún momento me algún comentario de
see the lawyer sent me a
hay que ver la abogada me ha puesto un
tweet she sent me two tweets I don't know what
tweet me ha puesto dos tweets no sé qué
some move like that no but I didn't give it
alguna movida así no pero yo no le di la
much importance just out of curiosity I
mayor importancia solo por curiosidad le
said let's see tell me who it is and and he says no I haven't
dije a ver dime quién es y y dice no he
deleted I haven't answered I don't know
borrado no le he contestado no sé alguna
something like that no I didn't give it more importance my
cosa así no no le di más importancia me
attention not because I said
llamaba la atención no porque dije
[ __ ] what lawyer did he hire
[__] que qué abogada habrá contratado
no who will the lawyer be Total yesterday I do
no quién será la abogada Total que ayer
n't know if it was because he retweeted it no I don't
No sé si fue porque él la retuiteó no no
know why not the move I am
sé por qué no se la movida estoy
often aware of the things that
pendiente muchas veces de las cosas que
are said about me and so on besides he is a
se hablan de mí y demás además es una
person e he is a person that I have
persona e es una persona a la que tengo
sued so H anything that
demandada entonces H cualquier cosa que
is preparing for the second
se está preparando para la segunda
lawsuit as well No well I take a
demanda también No pues yo le echo un
look at the Site it doesn't cost me anything and when I
vistac Sito no me cuesta nada y cuando
can I gossip okay Total that he
puedo cotilleo vale Total
retweeted me not this that they were
que que me retuiteó no esto que estaban
arguing about if it was  legal or not
discutiendo sobre si era legal o no
legal share screenshots of the
legal compartir pantallazos de la de la
car no an eagle kiss
de la del auto no un beso águila
Thank you very much today I have not set a
Muchísimas gracias hoy no he puesto
goal but I trust that you are going to
objetivo pero Confío en que Vais a
support this live a lot with super
apoyar muchísimo este directo con super
chat with member and with anything goes HM they
chat con miembro y con todo vale HM
were discussing the issue of
estaban discutiendo sobre el tema de que
well what we discussed yesterday no that it
bueno lo que comentamos ayer no que
seems to be illegal eh about
parece ser que es ilegal eh lo de lo de
publishing the order of a procedure no
publicar el auto de un procedimiento no
that is still in preliminary proceedings
que todavía está en diligencias previas
no we do not know what will happen and then they
no no se sabe qué va a pasar y entonces
were like arguing No
estaban como discutiendo No la abogada
his lawyer says that nothing happens because it has been
de él dice que no pasa nada porque se ha
filed and I uh the truth is I think that let's
archivado y yo eh la verdad pienso que
see it has not been definitively filed
que a ver no se ha archivado definitivo
until while there is an appeal
hasta que mientras que cabe recurso
yet no that is
todavía
not closed then Well I don't
no eso no está cerrado entonces Bueno no
know in the end it would be a fine eh I mean it
sé al final sería una multa eh o sea que
is not a legal thing or anything like that it
tampoco es una cosa legal ni ni nada por
would be a fine and little more if
el estilo sería una multa y poco más si
At the discretion of the judge decided it which
A discreción del juez lo decidiera que
I think he will not even get into that I don't know
yo creo que ni se meterá en eso no sé
Pablo thinks so I I think
Pablo piensa que sí yo yo creo que no se
the judge will not get into that to resolve But
meterá el juez en eso a resolver Pero
well whatever is okay
bueno lo que sea vale
Eh I'll start to see clear retweeted one
Eh me pongo a ver claro retuiteado una
lawyer and I start looking dig let's see
abogada y me pongo a ver dig vamos a ver
but this lawyer is the one in the case and such and
pero esta abogada es la del caso y tal y
I start looking at her tweets And yes, she is a
me pongo a ver sus tweet Y sí es una
lawyer who is handling the case, who is handling your
abogada que lleva el caso que lleva su
case, she is your lawyer,
caso es su abogada
okay, by pure chance I say, I'm going to
vale por pura casualidad digo voy a
look at her Twitter account a little bit It
mirar un poquito su cuenta de
never fails,
Twitter No falla
man It never fails
tío No falla
Eh This is what laser len's lawyer thought
Eh Esto es lo que opinaba la abogada de
when they sue me, okay, 25 of the 9th, the
cuando a mí me demandan vale 25 del 9 el
19th, responding to the news about
19 que respondiendo al a la noticia de
faca, okay, there are people who have nothing
faca vale hay gente que no tiene nada
Clear the difference and the limits between
Clara la diferencia y los límites entre
freedom of expression, gossip, and bullying
libertad de expresión salseo y Bullying
and if on top of that you do it with the intention of profit,
y si encima lo haces con Ánimo de lucro
this is what the lawyer thought about the
esto es lo que opinaba la abogada de del
issue of saying hair, crazy old broom
tema de de decir pelo escoba vieja loca
No, I don't remember, one day I have to
No no me acuerdo un día me tengo que
get the list because we mention it
poner la lista porque lo mencionamos
a lot, no, what are the terms under which they
mucho no Cuáles son los términos por los
sued me No, that was
que a mí me demandaron No eso era
bullying, that was bullying, okay, that was
bullying eso era bullying vale eso era
bullying and it was outside of freedom
Bullying y estaba fuera de la libertad
of expression on top of that, I did it, uh, with the
de expresión encima Yo lo hacía eh con
intention of profit, No, apart from this tweet,
Ánimo de lucro No aparte de este tweet
the lawyer It turns out that she is  friend
pues la abogada Resulta ser que es amiga
of Mrs. Antonia for many
de la señora Antonia de hace muchísimos
years okay I mean the fact that they're giving her
años vale o sea a mí lo de que le pongan
a lawyer is driving me crazy no Let's see no
un abogada me tiene loco no A ver no
wait for something else no no no he can't be
espera otra cosa no no no no puede estar
more caught okay he can't be more
más cogido vale no puede estar ya más
caught eh in history no longer the
agarrado eh en la historia ya no el
fact that they have they have
hecho de que te hayan de que te hayan
thrown a cape at you they haven't
echado un capotillo no te hayan
given you a lawyer eh it's very good I'm
presentado una abogada eh es muy bueno
happy for you it's not happening yes it's
me alegro por ti no pasa que sí que es
true man it surprises me that she's
verdad hombre que me sorprende que sea
a lawyer who has tweets like
una una abogada que tiene tweet como
this one that you're seeing on screen
como este que estáis viendo en pantalla
okay she has tweets this lawyer
vale tiene tiene tweet esta abogada
where she applauded the first dismissal of the
donde aplaudía el primer archivo del
Argo case you know that the Argo case
caso argo ya sabéis que el caso argo
before going to trial was dismissed twice
antes de llegar a juicio se archivó dos
and the lawyer said that it's very good
y la la abogada decía que está muy bien
that it seemed very good to her and that she hoped it would
que le parecía muy bien y que ojalá se
stay that way no no it stayed that way in the
quedara en eso no no se quedó en eso al
end but well she she wished it no that she hoped it would
final pero bueno ella ella lo deseaba no
stay that way
que ojalá se quedase en eso
m and she also has tweets
m y también tiene twit
saying well she answers almost all of
diciendo bueno contesta casi todos los
these people's tweets retweets almost all of
twits de esta gente retweet casi todos
these people's okay she's a friend of the
lo de esta gente vale es amiga de la
mother of  miare has been saying for many years
madre de miare de hace muchísimos años
that Dallas is going
asegura en su que que Dallas en
to fall at any moment okay
cualquier momento ya va a caer vale Ya
Dallas is going to fall right now Okay and he has a
mismo Dallas va a caer Okay y y tiene un
tweet for example where he claims that Dallas
twit por ejemplo donde afirma que Dallas
is an abuser Okay he says that Dallas
es un maltratador Vale dice que Dallas
has clearly
claramente ha hecho un maltrato
psychologically abused his ex so well eh I didn't
psicológico a su ex así que bueno eh No
fail I imagined that the shots were going
fallé me lo imaginaba que los tiros Iban
this way and no I wasn't wrong he has
por aquí y no me no me equivoqué tiene
another tweet where he says that he really likes
otro twet donde dice que le gusta mucho
the movie bocadillo anyway this
la película de bocadillo en fin este
guy
tipo
[Music]
[Música]
of this type of topic by the way yesterday I was
de este tipo de tema por cierto ayer
reviewing this tweet yesterday I reviewed these
revisando este tweet ayer revisado estos
tweets you know what I realized is that
tweet sabéis de lo que me di cuenta de
Rubén Sánchez The one with the knife has
que Rubén Sánchez El de faca ha
deleted all the tweets he had
eliminado todos los tweets que tenía
defending that Marlos and Argos were not
defendiendo que marlos y Argos no eran
the same dog and that I was kind of stupid
el mismo perro y que yo era medio lelo
I was kind of stupid Because I thought that
yo era medio lelo Porque yo pensaba que
I couldn't differentiate greyhounds okay
que yo no sé diferenciar los galgos vale
he had several tweets where he defended that the one with the
él tenía varios twits donde defendía eso
knife okay the one who releases the news
el de faca vale el que saca las noticias
and he deleted them the TT he deleted them
y los ha borrado los TT los ha borrado
this week because I recently saw them
esta semana porque hace poco los vi de
again okay he deleted them okay for whatever reason  the
nuevo vale los ha borrado vale por lo
best thing is he doesn't want us to blame him for
que sea a lo mejor no quiere que le
not being accurate in his
echemos en cara que no acierta
predictions, no, it's something he
pronóstico no que es una cosa que él me
recently told me on Twitter, which of
dijo hace poco en Twitter a la que por
course I didn't pay any [ __ ] attention to
supuesto no le hice ni ni puñetero caso
because the truth is I care very little or
porque la verdad me importa entre poco y
nothing about the nonsense they talk, no, but
nada la las tonterías que hablen no pero
look, thinking No, look, thinking, it
fíjate que pensando No fíjate pensando
already seemed striking to me, I don't say that you have to
ya me pareció llamativo no di que te que
take one, trust yourself where you've gotten yourself
tienes que [__] una fíate tú dónde te
into, how involved you are in
has metido hasta dónde estás metido en
the matter, not in something that wasn't yours,
el tema no en una cosa que no iba
that they even had to give you
contigo que hasta te han tenido que
the lawyer, they introduced you to a
poner la abogada te han presentado una
lawyer, no, why, surely Well, it
abogada no para que seguramente Pues
will be a favor, no, I don't know if she will charge you
será un favor no no sé si te cobrará
a lot or a little, no, but anyway, then they
mucho o poco no pero bueno Luego se
mess with Pablo, no, Pablo, he works
meten con Pablo no Pablo Pablo trabaja
for a carton of wine, they told him, no, well,
por un cartón de vino le decían no bueno
anyway, going around it, man, going around it,
Total que dándole vuelta
eh, What's up, Caela, how are you, honey, it sounds familiar, it sounds familiar to
eh Qué pasa caela Cómo estás
me, the subject of the
suena me suena el tema de que el
logo, I see the lawyer's logo and it
logotipo veo el logotipo de la abogada y
sounded really familiar to me and it came
me sonaba un montón y se me vino del
to my head at once, man, it came to my
tirón a la cabeza tío se me vino a la
head at once, don't you know, who
cabeza del tirón a que no sabéis Quién
is this
es esta
lawyer, who I don't
abogada
know  Who is this
a qui no sab Quién es esta
lawyer Well this lawyer already
abogada Pues esta abogada ya tuvo ya
had contact with me in 2019
tuvo un contacto conmigo en el año 2019
because when another of these
porque cuando otro de los amigos de esta
people's friends decided to mess with me,
gente se le dio por meterse conmigo
even calling me out on things, well, the
incluso poniéndome strike bueno cogió el
guy got really angry because of some
tío una s ardió muchísimo por unos
videos that I made of him You can't
vídeos que le hice No e los podéis
find them around here, I don't remember the
encontrar por ahí no me acuerdo de los
titles, the director of the movie
títulos el director de la película de
Miare or something like that, okay, he got really angry,
miare o algo así vale eh se ardió
the
muchísimo el
man called me out on things, he insulted me, he said
hombre me puso strike me insultó me dijo
a lot of things, no Luis
un montón de cosas no Luis
gendera Luis endera, I mean, they
gendera Luis endera o sea le le
introduced him to him, well, they were from the same group,
presentaron bueno eran del mismo grupo
not these Twitter people, she's not the
no de esta gente de Twitter no le es la
same lawyer, it already surprised me at the
misma abogada que ya me extrañó a m en
time that Luis Henda sent me an email
su momento que Luis henda me mandase un
from a lawyer from the other end
de parte de una abogada de la otra punta
of the Peninsula, you know And the fact is that she's the
de la Península sabes Y es que es la
lawyer who's a friend of these people, they don't appoint
abogada amiga de esta gente no le ponen
these people a lawyer so that they
una abogada esta gente para que me
insult me, not so that they insult
tengan insultando no para que me estén a
me, no,
mí a mí insultado no
and it's
e
important Luis gendera damn Luis let's see
importante Luis gendera [__] Luis a ver
Luis gendera you don't know Who is Luis
Luis gendera no sabéis Quién es Luis
gendera is this one who said some things  very
gendera es este que decía unas cosas muy
strange on Twitter not here put Well
extrañas en Twitter no por aquí puso
I made a few videos
Bueno le hice yo unos cuantos de vídeos
compiling that he had some tweets that are
recopilando que tenía unos tweet que son
a little
un po
bit a little strange no I don't know they are some
poco un poco raros no no sé son unos
twit Well the same as the serl Look
twit Bueno lo mismo que las serl Mira
before they went public he
antes de que salieran en público él te
was already insinuating that he knew about the
iba ya insinuando que sabía sobre los
procedures no This was when This
procedimientos no Esto fue cuando Esto
was the day that the lawsuit came to me
fue el día que a mí me llega la demanda
aguil a kiss this was the day that
aguil un beso este fue el día que a mí
the lawsuit came to me from these people the
me llegó la demanda de esta gente la
first lawsuit that they filed against me okay he
primera demanda que me pusieron vale é
puts it on Twitter just like today it's ler
lo pone en Twitter igual que hoy es ler
len that when they file something for
len el que cuando le archivan algo a
these people or whatever he's the first to
esta gente o lo que sea es el primero en
announce it before his own that his
anunciarlo antes que la propia que la
own insulted me okay he insulted me he
propia me insultaba vale me insultaba me
provoked me okay me adala Well
me me provocaba vale a mí adala Bueno
adala has said everything to mre he
adala le ha dicho de todo a mre le
hit on my father he said that if it
tiraba la caña a mi adre dijo que si no
weren't because he knew the
fuera porque conocía a la
mother I don't know what no Well here it said that he
madre no sé qué no Bueno aquí decía que
wanted to ask her to be his girlfriend But well
quería pedirle ser su novia Pero bueno
if he does it Luis gendera at 50 and something
si lo hace Luis gendera con 50 y tantos
years old no nothing happens no that's a joke that
años no no pasa nada no ese es broma ese
was a joke no well let's see you  I say one
era broma no bueno a ver te digo una
thing laen he calls me old,
cosa laen a m me llama viejo
someone called him a dirty old man because of the
al un pasa lo llamó viejo verde por los
audios that are out there of him that I
audios que hay por ahí de él que yo los
have
tengo
here I don't know what
aquí no sé qué
they will think
opinarán
about his lawyer friend I don't know what I don't know what
sobre su compadre de abogada no sé lo
later by the way there was a
que no s lo que luego por cierto hubo un
Lore What happens is that the subject is over
Lore Lo que pasa que ya se acabó el tema
but this man has continued to mess
pero este hombre se ha seguido metiendo
with me during the During every time he has
conmigo durante el Durante cada vez que
had the opportunity he has put t
ha tenido la oportunidad ha puesto t
about me I have them all saved no and
sobre mí los tengo todos guardados no y
then they came out to fac well I don't remember there
luego salieron a fá bueno no me acuerdo
was Ah I don't remember I would have to see it
hubo Ah no me acuerdo tendría que verlo
but there was a story there a friend
pero hubo una historia por ahí un amigo
started to joke because of a story between
empezó a funaro por una historia entre
the woman and the friend or or him with the friend
la mujer y el amigo o o él con el amigo
or him with the I don't remember a story they are
o él con la no me acuerdo una historia
messing with each other
se están metiendo los unos con los otros
that Hey if one day this these guys come back I have
que Oye si algún día vuelve este este
several several
lores que tengo pensado varias varias
series in my head About this guys
series en la cabeza Sobre este lores
because they don't stop provoking me and
porque no paran de provocarme y de
poking me in the end there will be a
pincharme de pincharme al final va un
day when my answer will not be liked and
día en que no va a gustar mi respuesta y
and I have a series in mind I have
y tengo pensado una una serie Tengo
a series in mind but I will tell you
pensado una serie pero ya os comentaré
what it is about because there are several things that
de qué va porque hay varias cosas que
still  I took out I didn't comment and so on
todavía no saqué no comenté y demás no
but well this lawyer this lawyer
pero bueno que esta abogada esta abogada
who accuses me of crimes who accuses
que me imputa delitos a mí que le imputa
Dala of crimes who thinks it's okay that
delitos a dala que le parece bien que
when there are crimes the
cuando sí que hay delitos se archiven la
case is archived this lawyer Okay,
causa esta abogada Vale
well she sent me a burua one day
pues me mandó un burua en su día
telling me that if I didn't delete
diciéndome que si yo no borraba los
Luis Endera's videos they were going to file
vídeos de Luis endera me iban a poner
another lawsuit against me, I tore it up here we put it
otra demanda yo la rompí aquí la pusimos
on a fan And I told the man
en un ventilador Y yo le dije al hombre
that if he wanted to agree on something to
que si quería acordar algo que me
take TR off me and I would remove the videos with
quitara TR y yo quitaba los vídeos con
Chulería and with ego I didn't want to be
Chulería y con ego no quería quedar por
above you I'm above you because
encima yo quedo por encima tuya porque
these people don't want to e
esta gente no no quieren
these people don't want to mediate or for the
e esta gente no quieren mediar ni que se
problems to end these people want to
acaben los problemas esta gente quieren
be above humiliate you badly
quedar por encima humillarte mal
trample on you so the day I told him
pisotearte entonces yo en su día le dije
Luis I sent him an email Also take away the
Luis Le mandé un email Además quíteme
strike take away the strike
usted el strike quíteme usted el strike
because I have a penalty on the channel and
que tengo una penalización en el canal y
I will delete the videos that you
yo borro los vídeos que que usted me
tell me that they offend you I didn't want to
diga que usted le ofenden no me no quiso
delete them I mean if you want me to
borrar los no quiso O sea si tú quieres
remove the videos Tell me  Take away
que quite los los vídeos Dímelo Quítame
the strike and I'll take it off But he didn't want to
el strike y yo quito Pero no quiso
because he wanted to humiliate no no well
porque él quería humillar no no pues
watch out in fact recently I have a
cuid de hecho hace poco tengo aquí un
tweet here that this lawyer is mocking me and
tweet que que la abogada esta se mofa y
says this when I get the the the
dice esto cuando me llega la la la
sentence of Joan Plana the director
sentencia de Joan plana lo del director
That is super classic incredible that she comes back
Ese es superclásico increíble que vuelva
Yes if they want they can come back that I no no no no I don't
Sí si ellos quieren pueden volver que yo
have any kind of
no no lo no no tengo ningún tipo de
problem that the The Movida is that
problema que la La Movida es que
The Movida is that this lawyer
La Movida Es que la abogada esta también
has also put T I mean I'm thinking if it
ha puesto T O sea estoy pensando si
could be the lawyer who is
puede ser la abogada que le esté
taking him to Tania's because if
llevando a lo a lo de Tania porque como
that is the plot T I'm already doing a somersault
ese sea el plot T yo ya hago voltereta
that they are putting a
de que le estén poniendo una amiga
lawyer friend to all of these already I really
abogada a todos estos ya de verdad me
throw myself on the ground no la la
tiro al suelo no
this lawyer I have seen her
la la la abogada esta la he visto
titting I was also looking yesterday dig
teteando También estuve mirando ayer dig
to see who she is hanging out with no and with Joan
a ver con quién se codea no y con Joan
Planas too on the subject of Tania she
planas también sobre el tema de Tania
has TT too and the whole thing is worth
tiene TT también y toda la movida vale
eh Javi has to Well there are many
eh Javi tiene para Bueno yo hay muchas
things that I have not taken out because they are already
cosas que no he sacado porque ya son
issues that were left no I do not live in 2019
temas que quedaron no no vivo en el 2019
or 2016 like they do  but yes there is an issue there are
ni el 2016 como ellos pero sí hay tema
little things there are little things there are series
hay cositas hay cositas que hay series
that can be good But well, that's it
que pueden ser buena Pero bueno ya está
for me if they leave me alone I
a mí si me dejan tranquilo Yo también
'm also very calm I live very peacefully
estoy muy tranqui yo vivo muy tranquilo
I have no problem for me this is
yo no tengo problema para mí esto es
work and that this lawyer makes fun
trabajo e que esta abogada se cachondea
of me [ __ ] with Luis gendera and says
de mí teteando con Luis gendera y pone
Javi has continued to mention Luis
Javi ha seguido mencionando a Luis
gendera when years have passed and
gendera cuando cuando han pasado años y
then he asks that they let go of his arm both
luego pide que le suelten el brazo tanto
on YouTube and Twitch now that he is
en YouTube como en Twitch ahora que está
deleting videos and he seems so
borrando vídeo y se muestra tan
conciliatory maybe it would be time to
conciliador igual sería el momento de
ask him to delete yours and ignore you
pedir que borre los tuyos y te ignore
with chafing I don't understand this t with
con sarnilla no yo entiendo este t con
chafing with joking no and he says Luis
sarnilla con cachondeo no y dice Luis
gendera is interested in doing it if not he will have to
gendera le interesa hacerlo si no tendrá
save a little more than I have to
que ahorrar un poco más que yo tengo que
save Luis gendera why do I have to
ahorrar Luis gendera para qué tengo yo
save for
ahorrar para
what why why haven't you given it has
qué por qué tú no has han dado han
been more than 4 years since those videos in
pasado más de 4 años de esos vídeos de
fact it's been six or so
hecho han pasado seis o sea está
the right to honor has expired it expires
prescrito el derecho al honor prescribe
after 4 years what do I have to save for what
a los 4 años que tengo que ahorrar para
why do I have to
qué para qué tengo que
save But well they are like that Or so like that no there is no
ahorrar Pero bueno son así O sea así que
more or so  are they a
no no hay más o sea son
bluffer? are they? well, these stories aren't it?
farolero son en fin estas historias no
but the thing that really caught my
pero la movida que a mí me llama mucho
attention yesterday when Ler Len gave her
la atención de ayer cuando ler len caela
a kiss
un beso
and among other things he talked about the
e entre otras cosas hablaba de de la
complaint that was filed against him, that there are
denuncia que le han puesto no que hay
a lot of lies in that complaint. Hey, it strikes
muchas mentiras en esa denuncia pues Oye
me that after
me llama la atención que después de
knowing this they
Saber esto ellos hayan
claimed that he has no
alegado que no tiene ningún tipo de
contact whatsoever with any, no
contacto con ningun ningún tipo de
relationship with Antonia, with Mrs.
relación con Antonia con la señora
Antonia who says Lerl has said this
Antonia que dice lerl esto lo ha dicho
in public, let's say he said it, he's
en público vamos lo ha dicho se está
defending himself in the lawsuit like this. No, I
defendiendo en la demanda así No yo no
have no relationship with that lady and
tengo ninguna relación con esa señora y
here he's put it to me again, eh, it's
aquí me la ha vuelto a poner eh que es
like, man, how are you going to put this in public?
como tío có vas a poner esto en público
Let's say not what I have in calls
vamos ya no lo que yo tengo en llamadas
and things, but [ __ ], he himself has
y en cosas sino [__] que é mismo se ha
publicly claimed to have information about
aado públicamente de tener informaciones
the trials before anyone else, having
de Los juicios antes que nadie habber
seen the videos of the trials, the
visto los vídeos de Los juicios las
sentences before anyone else, put it aside, I
sentencias antes que nadie la aparte yo
have calls with him where he tells me
tengo llamadas con él donde él me dice
the contact he has. No, but how are you going to,
el contacto que tiene No pero cómo vas a
how are you going to take it publicly and you're going to
cómo vas a [__] públicamente y me vas a
tell me what relationship I have with the
decir Qué relación tengo yo con la
lady, man, please, but well, yes, it
señora hombre por favor pero bueno sí
's put  even the lawyer is presented
que está puest está presentado hasta la
No, I don't care about giving
abogada No a mí lo de que le pongan un
these people a lawyer so they can keep
abogado a esta gente ya para que me siga
insulting me so they have us there
insultando para que nos tenga ahí a un
insulting a guy No, it drives me crazy
tío insultando No a mí me tiene loco
because of course yesterday we were seeing what
porque claro ayer Estuvimos viendo lo de
yesterday we were seeing that
que ayer Estuvimos viendo lo de que él
when he has to respond to
cuando tenga que responder a las
our lawsuits he's going to say that
demandas nuestras él va a decir que que
your honor I think he should
que su señoría Yo pienso que debería
insult them a lot better
insultarlos mucho más vale
lerl he says that civil lawsuits
lerl que dice que las demandas civiles
don't have witnesses okay he says he's
no tienen testificales vale él dice que
going to go to court and he's going to say Hey hey hey
va a llegar al juzgado y va a decir Oye
Mr. Judge I think
oye oye señor juez yo creo que estaremos
you and I will agree that I have to
usted y yo de acuerdo en que a Javi lo
insult Javi a lot more because
tengo que insultar mucho más por qué
because Javi said that Dallas didn't
Porque Javi ha dicho que que Dallas no
file a false complaint against me okay I
me ha puesto una denuncia falsa vale Yo
think that is more than
creo que eso es motivo más que
justified reason for me to insult him a lot
justificado para que yo lo insulte mucho
more for a lot of years no and Well
más durante un montón de años no y Bueno
and sometimes I freak out no because
e a veces a mí yo yo flipo no porque de
suddenly there are people who are like very
repente hay gente que está como muy
sensitive about the right to honor and
sensibilizada con el derecho al honor y
they are very affected by four or five insults
la afectan mucho cuatro o cinco insultos
but then they support a guy who is
pero luego apoyan a un tío que te está
insulting you every day for years
insultando todos los días durante años
but oh well  Of course I understand a little about what this is about.
pero bueno claro Yo entiendo un poco de
I think that people do
lo que va la cosa yo creo que la gente
too. I think that people who know how to
también yo creo que la gente que sabe
write. I think that people know how to
escribir Yo creo que la gente sabe
write, read, walk on both legs.
escribir leer andar con las dos piernas
I think that people know more or less
Yo creo que la gente sabe más o menos de
what this is about. Don't obsess, how
lo que va la vaina No obsesiones qué
bad obsessions are.
malas son las obsesiones
[Music]
[Música]
No, today he dedicated another live show to me. Okay.
No hoy me ha vuelto a dedicar un directo
I've already said it and I'll
vale Yo ya lo he dicho y lo vuelvo a
repeat it. I have no problem with people
repetir yo no tengo ningún problema en
dedicating live shows to me.
que en que a mí se me dediquen directos
Okay, I mean, I don't name
vale o sea yo no pongo
anyone. Okay.
a nadie ninguno vale
No, I have no problem with
e yo no yo no tengo ningún problema con
people talking about me and being
que la gente hable de mí y que estén en
against me and criticizing me. In fact,
contra mí y que me critiquen De hecho
here we often react to
aquí reaccionamos muchas veces a las
criticism. What I'm not going to tolerate is, okay. What I'm
críticas yo lo que no voy a tolerar vale
not going to tolerate are insults,
Yo lo que no voy a tolerar son insultos
serious insults. I'm not offended because they
insultos graves yo no me ofendo porque
call me a wig or you don't know what I'm
me digan peluca o no sabes lo que te
saying, I mean, but man, I think that the
digo o sea pero hombre Yo creo que las
expressions that this guy uses towards
expresiones que este chico utiliza hacia
me. Well, I think they are not justified
mí Pues creo que no están justificadas
within the framework of freedom of
dentro del marco de de la libertad de
expression that he believes in. No, that he has.
expresión que él cree No que tiene
Well, in fact, that's what I'm telling you.
em Bueno de hecho es lo que te digo O
whether they sentenced
sea si condenaron a si condenaron a a
nauter for saying bastard
nauter por por decir cabronazo
MM mongolito
MM mongolito
and [ __ ] you're my [ __ ] or something like that No
y putita eres mi putita o algo así No
man, well I think that the expressions
hombre pues yo creo que las expresiones
of this man are not justified
de este hombre no están justificadas
because I do not address him with that term
porque yo no me dirijo a él ese término
he says no no it's that look Javi oliveira
él dice no no es que mira Javi oliveira
mentions me man let's see I have no
me menciona hombre a ver no me queda
other choice I have no other choice if you have a
otra no me queda otra si tienes un un
fight with Dallas review well
pleito con Dallas review pues
evidently it is an issue of gossip that
evidentemente es un tema de salseo que
must be discussed No I do not address you
hay que comentar No yo no me dirijo a ti
in the same terms okay or rather Joan
en los mismos términos vale o sea Joan
planas also got involved he was messing
planas también se metier se metía
with me and they sentenced me Because they said
conmigo y me condenaron Porque dijeron
that my expressions were very
que mis expresiones eran muy
disproportionate it was you F you how
desproporcionadas fuite tú F tú cómo
will yours be not the serl But hey
Serán las tuyas no la serl Pero oye
Well you you get there full that I think
Bueno tú tú llegas allí llen que yo creo
that maybe the judge and the prosecutor say what
que a lo mejor el juez y el fiscal dice
you say Hey we have to insult him
lo que tú dices Oye hay que insultarlo
much more laen insult
mucho más laen insúltame
me ​​they have called my attention
me han llam la atención respecto
regarding what he said today okay well
respecto a lo que ha dicho hoy vale
This is the issue of
bueno Esto es lo del tema de los
insults
insultos
okay in my first lawsuit attentive
vale en la primera demanda mía atentos
eh
eh
eh you claim that I'm a bad [ __ ]
eh afirmas que yo soy una mala [__]
person the worst that exists on the internet
persona lo peor que existe en internet
[ __ ] but let's really see what you
cabrón pero vamos a ver de verdad qué
want me to contribute to the judge Imagine
quieres que le aporte al juez Imagínate
this is real look listen that it's
que esto es real mir escucha que está
already filed in that court what
presentada ya en ese juzgado lo que no
you haven't notified okay eh you claim that
estás tú notificado vale eh afirmas que
I'm a bad [ __ ] person the worst that
yo soy una mala [__] persona lo peor que
exists on the internet [ __ ] dirty old man crazy
existe en internet cabrón viejo verde
infected garbage filthy pig clown I mean I mean
chalado basura infecta cerdo guarro
how do you want me to argue to a
decir cómo quieres que le argumente a un
judge that I think you're a bad person a
juez que me pareces una mala persona un
crazy person and a
chalado y un
clown I still if I were only a
payaso yo todavía si solamente fuera
bad person clown and a crazy
mala persona payaso e chalado dentro de
within what we do I wouldn't
dentro de a lo que nos dedicamos no me
start filing a lawsuit for that
pongo a poner una demanda por eso
okay the problem is that there are some more
vale el problema es que hay algunas más
the problem is that it's day to day I
el problema es que es el día a día le
can argue is that I think about it What do you
puedo argumentar es que lo pienso Qué
want me to
quieres que te
say Well that you think let's see
diga Bueno eso de que lo piensas a ver
clearly I can't I ca
claro yo yo no
n't say everything I
puedo yo no puedo decir todo lo que
think I think a lot of things about a lot of
pienso yo pienso muchas cosas de muchas
people but I can't say everything I
gente pero no puede decir todo lo que
think I mean and there are a lot of people that I say
piensa o sea y hay mucha gente que digo
This is a pedophile and I don't say it
Este es un pederasta y no lo digo
obviously you can't say it This is
evidentemente no puedes decirlo Esta es
a [ __ ]  you filthy [ __ ] I can't
una [__] [__] asquerosa no puedo
say it This is a piece of [ __ ] I
decirlo Este es un pedazo de [__] no lo
can't say it obviously you can't
puedo decir evidentemente tú no puedes
say what's on your mind about
decir lo que se te pasa por la cabeza de
people in the media eh and then when you
la gente en un medio eh que luego tú
speak in private
hablando en privado
eh you can say what you see but of
eh tú puedes decir lo que tú veas pero
course you're going to get to the game and you're
claro que tú vas a llegar al juego y le
going to tell him it's what I think okay okay I do
vas a decir es que es lo que pienso vale
n't understand then the serl that you
vale No entiendo entonces la serl que
went to look for Delos the two or
fueses a buscar a delos la las dos o
three times that Delos has gone to
tres veces que delos está ha ido a a
offer an agreement okay the first time you did
ofrecer acuerdo vale que la primera vez
n't reach an agreement because it
no llegasteis a un acuerdo porque
hurt you that Delos told me
te dolió que que deos me lo contaras
here live fall a kiss
aquí en directo caela un beso
em and because of the fact that you want to
em y por el hecho de que quieres
pretend an image for that public
aparentar una imagen para ese público
that you have the truth the public cloth they
que tienes que la verdad el público tela
don't post comments they seem like robots they
no ponen comentarios parecen robot
seem like robots no
parecen robot no
e how can you not
e como no puedes
argue you have to pretend that I don't
argumentar tienes que aparentar eso no
know why the truth is that to
sé el Por qué la verdad yo es que para
be public it's not such no
ser público no tal no
emm But well why didn't you go all the
em Pero bueno por qué no llegaste hasta
way with Delos
el final con delo
and tell him it's that it's what I think that he
y le dijiste es que es lo que pienso que
is the biggest scammer on the internet that he is
es el mayor estafador de internet que es
garbage that he is [ __ ] all the
una basura que es una [__] todos los
insults that you had against Delo and the
insultos que le tenías a delo y las
accusations and charges of crime
acusaciones e imputaciones de delito Por
Why didn't you go all the way and make
qué no llegaste hasta el final y que
Delo pay the
delo palmse las
costs No, you can't say everything you
costas No tú no puedes decir todo lo que
think What do you want me to argue,
piensas Es que qué quieres que argumente
send me evidence that he's a
pruebas mándame pruebas de que es un
clown Well, I don't know what you want me to
payaso Pues no sé qué quieres que te
put you in a wig What do you want me to
ponga a ti con peluca Es que qué quieres
tell you is that I
que te diga es que lo
think I think you're a clown and
pienso yo pienso que eres un payaso y
I think you're a bad person What do you
pienso que eres una mala persona qué
want me to do?
quieres que
The only thing I want is to speak ill
haga lo único que quiero es hablar mal
of the actor when he does something good or something that
del actor cuando haga algo bueno o o le
benefits him I'm not going to talk about it exactly
beneficie no lo voy a hablar exactamente
when something good happens to you I'm not going to
cuando te pase algo bueno no lo voy a
talk about it and when something bad happens to you I
hablar y cuando te pase algo malo sí lo
will talk about it and you want me to tell the
voy a hablar y quieres que le diga al
judge well I'm going to tell the judge yes yes yes I'm
juez pues al juez le voy a decir sí sí
going to make fun of this man when bad things happen to him and when
cosas malas me voy a burlar y cuando le
good things happen to him I'm going to ignore him yes I'm
ocurran cosas buenas lo voy a ignorar sí
going to tell the judge that what do you want
voy a decirle eso al juez qué quieres
me to argue until yesterday until before I
que argumente yo hasta ayer hasta antes
found out Who was your lawyer I
de enterarme Quién era tu abogada Yo
thought that this type of statements
pensaba que este tipo de afirmaciones
that you made in public made
que tú la hicieras en público le hacían
your lawyer throw herself at her  hairs per
a tu abogada a tirarse de los pelos per
any lawyer tells you dude don't say
cualquier abogado te dice tío no digas
this I mean don't say don't say that
esto O sea no digas que no digas que
making videos insulting this
haciendo vídeos insultando a esta
person who sued you is where you make the most
persona que te ha demandado es donde más
money don't say that you want to
dinero ganas no digas que quieres
harm his job don't say that you
perjudicarle su trabajo no digas que
want to make him lose visits make him
quieres hacerle perder visita hacerle
lose
perder
donations okay in other words a person who
donaciones vale o sea una persona que
wants to take away another person's job
quiere quitarle el trabajo a otra a base
by tarnishing his image insulting accusing
de manchar su imagen insultar imputar
crimes of course
delitos claro
and you're saying that it's the only thing that
e Y estás diciendo que es lo único que
gives you money and you're saying that you
te da dinero y estás diciendo que
want them to donate less to me and that and
quieres que me donen menos y que y
take away what I have man son
quitarme lo que tengo hombre hijo me
is giving me the subject no I mean
está regalando el el tema no O sea
any lawyer but of course it turns
cualquier abogado pero claro es que
out that the lawyer of this man who
resulta que la abogada de este señor que
also accuses him of psychological abuse to
también le imputa maltrato psicológico a
dalla this lady With all due respect eh
dalla esta señora Con todo el respeto eh
Hey everyone does their job as like
Oye cada uno hace su trabajo como como
But well she talks about other lawyers
Pero bueno ella habla de otros abogados
eh I mean she has
eh O sea ella en su Twitter tiene
Pablo criticizing a lot of kisses to
criticando a Pablo un montón de bese a
a lot of lawyers eh I mean she criticizes
un montón de abogados eh o sea critica
criticizes lawyers no but no the lawyer does
critica abogados no pero no la abogada
n't call her attention the lawyer
no le llama la atención la abogada le
tells her Haha laser it's that you are a
dice Jaja láser es que eres un
sincere killer well sincere killer is the
sincericida bueno sincericida es el
term I  I call them camicas but well
término yo lo llamo camicas pero bueno
sincere killer let's see sincere is sun with
sincericida a ver sincero es sol con los
insults eagle a sincere kiss is
insultos águila un beso sincero es
only when it comes to insults because
solamente a la hora de insultar porque
then sincere is so-so because I already
luego sincero es regulín porque ya te
told you that you have defended that one of the
digo que habéis defendido que una de las
things that you have defended here but
cosas que habéis defendido aquí pero
well he has the right to lie in the
bueno él tiene derecho a mentir en el
procedure eh I mean it's not a problem if he lies I do
procedimiento eh o sea tampoco pasa nada
n't know what the point is
porque mienta no sé cuál es el Point
because what I want is to harm him
porque yo lo que quiero es perjudicarle
in his work I don't think he
en su trabajo eso no creo que lo haya
said that but well
dicho pero bueno
Thank you it benefited him I'm not going to talk about it
Gracias le beneficie no lo voy a hablar
exactly when something good happens to you I'm not
exactamente cuando te pase algo bueno no
going to talk about it and when something bad happens to you I
lo voy a hablar y cuando te pase algo
will talk about it and you want me to
malo sí lo voy a hablar y quieres que le
tell the judge well to the judge I'm going to tell him
diga al juez pues al juez le voy a decir
yes if you're going to tell him that I don't have
sí yo si le vas a decir eso no tengo
any kind of pega
ningún tipo de Pega
Eh yes yes when
Eh sí sí yo de este señor cuando le
bad things happen to this man I'm going to make fun of him and
ocurran cosas malas me voy a burlar y
when good things happen to him I'm going to
cuando le ocurran cosas buenas lo voy a
ignore him yes I'm going to tell the judge that what do you
ignorar sí voy a decirle eso al juez qué
want me to argue I don't know what the
quieres que argumente no sé cuál es el
point is the point is that if you talk about
Point el punto es que si tú hablas de
the gossip of a person you talk about the
los salseos de una persona hablas de los
gossip that benefits and  and that they do
salseos que benefician y y que le y que
not benefit him also because he is the
no le benefician también porque es la
person who is the subject that you deal with
persona que es la temática que tú tratas
okay the problem is that you are
vale el problema es que tú estás
saying that you want to harm my
diciendo que quieres perjudicar mi
work make me lose income
trabajo hacerme a mí perder ingresos
because you consider that I do not deserve
porque tú consideras que yo no merezco
what I have I think it is envy and
lo que tengo yo creo que es envidia e
that you would like very much to be in my place
que te gustaría mucho est en mi lugar
but
pero
that of course the problem is that you
que que claro el problema es que tú
are saying no longer that you deal with my
estás diciendo ya no que trates mis
issues because I am a public person
temas porque yo soy una persona pública
no no you are saying that you want to
no no tú estás diciendo que quieres
tarnish my image because it is the only thing that
manchar mi imagen porque es lo único que
gives you money and that you want to make
te da dinero y que quieres hacerme
me lose money then of course I do not know
perder a mí dinero entonces claro No sé
if you know how the issue works demand
si sabes cómo funciona el tema demanda
sirus a
sirus un
kiss that what I want is to
beso que yo lo que quiero es
harm him in his work I do not think he
perjudicarle en su trabajo eso no creo
said that You just explained it
que lo haya dicho Lo acabas de explicar
yourself Well apart from saying it
tú mismo Bueno aparte de decirlo
literally okay it will come to you
literalmente vale que ya te llegará
when it arrives You see it and check
cuando te llegue Tú lo ves y compruebas
the minute and the video thanks to me I
el minuto y el vídeo gracias a mí lo
have it certified and the videos are going to be
tengo certificad yos los vídeos se van a
presented in full
presentar todo entero
okay you just explained a similar thing, I
vale acabas de explicar una cosa similar
mean in some occasions you have told him
o sea en algunas ocasiones le has dicho
literally and in others you explain it like that no
literal y en otras lo explicas así no la
people there are already people who donate to him less than that he
gente ya hay gente que le dona meno que
has stopped following him there are people  that he has
ha dejado de seguirle hay gente que ha
stopped following him because of the things that I have
dejado de seguirle por las cosas que he
said and it is
dicho y es
legitimate, I feel the
legítimo yo me
same way. Well, you said it in public. I
esto mismo Bueno lo has dicho en público
mean, I don't care. I wasn't going to tell you. Say the
O sea me da igual No te iba a decir Di
same thing in front of the game, but if you
lo mismo delante del juego pero si lo
are saying it, you are
estás diciendo tú sea estás reconociendo
publicly acknowledging that you have caused me
públicamente que me has causado
harm. No, no, but for his followers.
perjuicio no no pero para los seguidores
Very, very cool, very cool. The dog from
suyos muy muy Guay muy Guay el perro de
Dallas. I don't know what, I don't know how much,
Dallas no sé qué no sé cuánto
dog. I don't know if it's a problem of, I do
perro lo no sé si es un problema de no
n't know the truth, I don't know what it is. eh, I'm in no
sé la verdad no sé lo que es eh
hurry, eh, I
yo no tengo ninguna prisa eh o sea yo ya
mean, I'm telling you, I have filed a lawsuit against you, I'm
te digo sea te he puesto una demanda te
going to file another one. I know that today you said
voy a poner otra sé que hoy has dicho
something that I don't know what he
algo de
said, I don't know what he
que no sé qué es lo que ha dicho no sé
said exactly, that
qué es lo que ha dicho exactamente que
if he had to apologize to me for something, no,
si me tenía que pedir perdón por algo no
the lawsuit has already been filed, that has
ya está la demanda puesta eso tiene unas
costs. My son, the only thing I would
costas hijo mío yo lo único que
accept is that you go to court if
aceptaría es que vayas a juicio si
you want, and I mean, I don't know if you go to court
quieres y o sea no sé que vayas a juicio
and say these things, that's it,
y digas estas cosas ya está sea que
pay what you have to pay. There is no
pagues lo que tengas que pagar Es que no
more. I mean, why would I forgive you for
hay más O sea por qué te voy a perdonar
a lawsuit, the only option there would be
una demanda la única opción que habría
is that you pay the costs and that  and what and
es que pagues las costas y y que y que y
other kinds of things I don't know but how am I
otro tipo de cosas No sé pero cómo me
going to spend money on something and
voy a gastar yo dinero en una cosa y
now I'm going to remove it but also if you
ahora la voy a quitar pero aparte si
keep insulting every
sigues insultando cada
day the things that I've said that are all
día las cosas que he dicho que son todas
true then there are people who have
verdad pues hay gente que se ha dado
realized I have my doubts you have said What they have
cuenta yo tengo mis dudas has dicho Lo
told you is true But
que te han dicho a ti que es verdad Pero
well you already present it there send
bueno eso ya tú lo presentas allí sender
a kiss you present it there without
un beso tú lo presentas allí sin
problem
problema
read that you don't have to follow you because you
ler de que no tiene que seguirte porque
don't deserve it What's the point I have
no lo mereces Cuál es el punto
n't seen it I haven't seen it When was it
no lo he visto no lo he visto Cuándo ha
at 8 in the afternoon is that I'm
sido a las 8 de la tarde es que estoy
really angry today
humado hoy de verdad
and my brother in Christ with so much
e mi hermano en Cristo con tanta marca
watermark if you want we can change the name of the
de agua si quieres cambiamos el nombre
club Javi
al club Javi
Oliveira Well listen let's see the issue
oliveira Bueno oye a ver es que el tema
of the watermark I've already explained
de la marca de agua ya lo he explicado
a lot of times I understand that I understand
un montón de veces entiendo que entiendo
that people say [ __ ] son of a [ __ ]
que la gente dice [__] hijo de [__] no
the content is not yours not to put a
es tuyo el contenido no para ponerle
watermark on it But the issue of the
marca de agua Pero el tema de la marca
watermark is eh Because basically then
de agua es eh Porque básicamente luego
a lot of a lot of channels that
un montón de un montón de canales que no
I'm not referring to Uncle Chur's channels and
me refiero a los canales del tío chur y
with which I get along because  I have
con los que me llevo porque yo con el
had one conversation with Uncle Chur
tío chur tengo hablado 1 conversaciones
that I can have about my content, whatever the
que pueda ha serer con mi contenido lo
hell he wants, and he has
que le salga del pene y él me ha dicho a
always told me the same thing about his, okay, I mean,
mí siempre lo mismo del suyo vale o sea
Uncle Shur,
el tío shur
eh, any of them, okay, they can take
eh cualquiera de ellos vale pueden [__]
my content and just like I upload a video,
mi contenido y tal y como subo un vídeo
upload it to their [ __ ] channel if they want, okay, I mean, I don't care,
subirlo a su [__] canal si quieren vale
but I know that then there are
o sea me da igual pero s que luego hay
a ton of channels,
un montón de canales de cuentas de
Twitter accounts and so on that are doing
Twitter y demás que está lugar haciendo
their job, okay, the guy who
su trabajo vale que encuentra el tío que
is a bookworm, the
es una rata de biblioteca encuentra el
guy finds any thing, okay, and he and he
tío cualquier movida Vale y el y el y
goes and steals it and there are entire videos,
coge y se lo roban y hay vídeos enteros
entire newscasts, entire channels that
noticieros enteros canales enteros que
make a living, well, since they make a living from this
que viven pues ya que viven de este
work, then you go with the
trabajo pues vas con con la marca de
watermark, no, I try not to make it look ugly, okay, I try not to make it look ugly, I don't think it looks bad, I don't think it looks bad, I don't think it
agua no yo intento que no quede feo vale
's very
queda No creo que creo que no es muy
invasive,
invasiva
okay,
vale
and it already has this frame that is very
Y ya tiene el marco este que es muy
recognizable as my Twitter account,
reconocible como de mi cuenta de Twitter
okay, and I give credit to the
vale Y le doy crédito al verdadero al
real owner of the content, you
verdadero dueño del contenido me
know, I mean, I don't know if Ali bothers him,
entiendes o sea no sé si Ali lo molesta
well, he can tell me and I can  don't
pues me lo puede decir y puedo no
comment But well I think that with this it
comentar Pero bueno creo que con esto se
also becomes fair use when
transforma también uso legítimo cuando
I'm reacting you understand you
yo estoy reaccionando me entiendes les
do the work for free for a lot of
haces el trabajo gratis a un montón de
people no no it's not that I do it It's not that
gente no no es que lo haga Yo no es que
I do it because this These are little things about
lo haga yo porque est Estos son cositas
places you understand these are little things about
de lugares me entiendes esto son cositas
places and and don't
de lugares y y no me
[ __ ] with me it touches my dick There are days when I
[__] toca la [__] Hay días que me
wake up and there are entire videos of work
levanto y son vídeos enteros del trabajo
from
de
places entire entire video of suit from
lugares entero entero vídeo de traj de
places of things that maybe have
lugares de cosas que a lo mejor han
happened live that they would never have seen
pasado en directos que no hubieran visto
in their [ __ ] life you understand So
en su [__] vida me entiendes Entonces
then it's done I put the watermark
pues ya está le pongo la marca de agua
so it's not invasive and that's it especially
que no sea invasiva y ya está sobre todo
Twitter accounts that steal your clips
cuentas de Twitter que te roban los clip
Yeah it's because of that or whatever but it's not my
Sí es por eso o sea pero no es mi
content I give credit to the so and so
contenido Yo le doy crédito al al tal y
and little else you understand me Club 113 are
y poco más me entiendes Club 113 son
haters of Dallas I think Well and mine or something
haters de Dallas creo Bueno y mío o sea
because gorgo well I understand that Nilo
porque el gorgo bueno entiendo que Nilo
heda doesn't have a bad feeling
heda no tiene mal rollo
about me I don't know if Nilo heda even follows me
conmigo no sé si me sigue incluso Nilo
but but gorgo man we had a
heda pero pero gorgo hombre tuvimos un
bad feeling because he did something nauter dirty to him
mal rollo porque le hizo una guarrada
in his time and we  We fought with
nauter en su tiempo y nos peleamos con
him really
él bien
hard going back to
fuerte volviendo a
this I really don't understand You have to
esto yo es que de verdad no entiendo Hay
be a really bad person Javi has
que ser muy mala persona Javi tiene
shady things behind his back he has done
cosas turbias por detrás ha hecho cosas
very very shady things it's true it's totally
muy muy chungas es verdad es totalmente
true totally true
cierto totalmente cierto
This is what he always reads I've
Esto es lo que lee siempre esto lo he
read this 250 times
leído 250 veces
okay more things or no this no longer thing that I do
vale más cosas o no esto ya no cosa que
n't want to read here on YouTube okay Yeah of
no quiero leer aquí en YouTube vale Ya
course he'll find them and what and let him
claro ya se las encontrará él y que y
answer this is day after day eh How
conteste esto es un día tras día eh Cómo
you like them eh Javi how you like
te gustan eh Javi cómo te gustan los
penises
penes
[Laughter]
[Risas]
Oh my God
Ay Dios mío
man No yeah yeah yes the insults you can
tío No sí si si los insultos te puedes
laugh a lot when you're that age How
reír mucho cuando tienes esa edad Qué
old is laser
edad tiene láser
60 but I'm telling you I mean the thing is that of
60 pero ya te digo O sea la movida es
course we've
que claro
seen convictions for much less
le hemos visto condenas por mucho menos
no but well eh that will
no pero bueno eh eso ya se discutirá
obviously be discussed in court okay and he doesn't
evidentemente en el juicio vale y no
admit to anything and he's on IG yeah it's like eh
reconoce nada y va de ig sí es como eh
man he's a person who's my age
tío es una persona que tiene mi edad en
actually joking aside he's not my
realidad fuera de bromas no tiene mi
age
edad
and I don't have the need to look
y yo no tengo la necesidad de quedar por
great Cool with children of like
lo alto de Guay con niños de o sea
because official like literally okay
porque oficial o sea literalmente vale
[Music]
[Música]
this These are not children  I mean, these are not
esto Estos no son niños o sea Estos no
people my age, like my
son personas de mi de mi edad Como mi
audience, but of course, let's see,
público pero claro es que a ver es que
the content he has is this:
el contenido que él tiene es este
calling Javi a dog, putting collars on him,
llamarle perro a Javi ponerle collares
putting dicks in his face
ponerle pollas en la cara
[Music]
[Música]
messing with Dala every day. I mean, he doesn't
meterse con dala todos los días O sea no
have any content. I truly understand,
tiene un contenido Yo entiendo de verdad
and I mean,
y o sea
sincerely, I don't prohibit
sinceramente que yo no no le prohíbo a
anyone from talking about me. I mean, what I
nadie que hable de mí o sea yo lo que
say is free within the terms of the
digo hbre dentro de los términos de los
parameters that we understand as legal,
parámetros que entendemos como legales
normal people are okay. I mean, and I think we've already
normal vale o sea y creo que ya hemos
seen more or less from other lawsuits that
visto más o menos por otras demandas que
have passed, what the legal terms are
han pasado no Cuáles son los términos
and what they aren't. To me, the fact that it
legales y cuáles no a mí el hecho de que
seems to him that I have lied here, that
él le parezca que yo he mentido aquí que
I am a hypocrite, his absolute right to
yo soy un hipócrita su plen simo derecho
do so, it would be lacking, it would be lacking that it
de hacerlo faltaría más faltaría más que
was my intention to censor him, he cannot
fuera mi intención censurar le no puede
speak what you want and give his opinion, and
hablar lo que tú quieras y opinar y y
everything that now, what you are not going to
todo lo que ahora lo que no me vas a
accuse me of are crimes like you have accused me of
imputar son delitos como me has imputado
several times, you will see in this lawsuit,
a varios lo verás en esta demanda sobre
especially in the second lawsuit because in the
todo en la segunda demanda porque en el
last year it has been but then that he does not
último año ha sido pero luego que no se
remember  of the things he says I don't
acuerda de las cosas que dice no se
remember you see it here then he is
acuerd lo ves aquí luego está
discovering new things he is
descubriendo cosas nuevas está
discovering new things in that I
descubriendo cositas nuevas em que yo
understand that it is the content that he has
entiendo que es el contenido que tiene
is this one more I have a lot of
es este qui más yo tengo muchísimo
content I am not going to dedicate myself to a
contenido yo no me voy a dedicar a un
rify raff with him, I only when it is
rify raff con él yo solamente cuando es
a topic like this, not like for example this of
un tema así no como por ejemplo esto de
the complaint, then I have to mention it
la denuncia pues lo tengo que mencionar
or when he comes out debating with someone
o cuando sale debatiendo con alguien
but I have a lot of other content,
pero yo tengo otro mucho contenido
a lot of content, a lot of
muchísimos contenidos muchísimos
guests, a lot of topics, a lot of
invitados muchísimos temas muchísimas
series, a lot of things that I try to
series muchísimas cosas que intento
do okay Mm what can I tell you Look what he
hacer vale Mm qué te digo Mirad lo que
said here okay now on the subject of
ha dicho aquí vale ya sobre el tema de
his
su
complaint this is him explaining
denuncia esto es él explicando el Por
why in the trial he without anyone
qué en el juicio él sin que nadie le
asking him has given details of
pregunte ha dado detalles de
what Dallas's house is like
Cómo es la casa de
if he hasn't been there okay Well
Dallas si no ha estado allí vale Bueno
he explains it okay Look at the
pues él lo explica vale Mirad la
explanation now
explicación ahora bien
when in the interrogation of Dallas
cuando en el interrogatorio a Dallas
the other party comes and tells him but in his
viene la otra parte y le dice pero en su
house on the slope below no one is not and
casa en la cuesta parabajo no s no sos y
such he already answers but he told you there it is
tal yas le contesta pero a te ha dich
downstairs in my house how do you
hay está para abajo en mi casa cómo lo
know there are details of that of course there
sabes ahí hao detalles de eso claro ahí
when the other party gives details  of what
cuando la otra parte da detalles de cómo
the house in Dallas is like,
es la casa de Dallas
eh, I'm going to give some information that is
eh voy a dar una información que es
extremely good, I don't know, maybe I
extremadamente bueno no lo sé a lo mejor
understand that this is the nursing home and you don't
entiendo que esto es el geriátrico y no
know it. But there is
lo saben Pero existe una
something
cosa que se
called, called Google, okay, I know that
llama se llama Google vale sé que a lo
maybe we don't have it very determined, there are
mejor no lo tenemos muy determinado
various ways to get
existen vari varias maneras de conseguir
images. Now, I
imágenes ahora
looked it up on
bien lo busqué en
Google. But why. I mean, how come you have
Google Pero por qué O sea cómo que has
given information about what's in the
dado información de lo que hay en la
house in Dallas if you haven't been there, I
casa de dalla si no has estado allí lo
looked it up on Google.
miré en Google
This is tremendous, pay attention to this. Because
esto es tremendo atentas a esta Porque
a big melon is opening here, eh,
aquí se abre un melón gordo eh aquí se
a big melon is opening here,
abre un melón gordo
eh, that it may also be
eh que igualmente
possible, that it may also be possible to
podrá que igualmente podrán podrán
win it, they won't be able to win it. I'm not getting involved in that,
ganarlo no podrán ganarlo Yo ahí no me
okay. The only thing I'm getting involved in is
meto vale Yo lo único que me meto es en
that the one who is claiming me is
que aquí me está reclamando a mí el que
claiming me, I don't know what to put it in. I
me está reclamando no sé que ponlo Yo
think that it is not a
pienso que no es una denuncia
false accusation, in other words, you think that it is a
falsa o sea que piensas que es una
real accusation, in other words, here he just
denuncia real o sea que aquí acaba de
asserted in front of 1,454 people that he
aseverar delante de 1454 personas que él
believes that I went to the house in Dallas,
cree que yo fui a casa de Dallas
threatened to kill him and steal
amenazarle de muerte y a robarle
packages, in other words, implicitly what he is
paquetes o sea implícitamente lo que
doing here  is to accuse me of a
está haciendo aquí es imputar me un
crime of an accuser to accuse me in front of
delito de un imputar imputar delante de
1450 people who thinks that I went to
1450 personas que piensa que yo fui a
rob him is
robarle está
fine according to him that I say that I say
bien según él que yo diga que yo diga
that I do not see evidence of a false complaint
que yo no veo indicios de una denuncia
okay eh that I am accusing him of crimes okay
eh que le estoy imputando delitos vale
But why I mean where that it
Pero por qué O sea en dónde que
still does not reach it does not reach they will be
igualmente no llega no llega podrán
able to win it they will not be able to win it I do not get involved in that okay The
ganarlo no podrán ganarlo Yo ahí no me
only thing I get involved in is
meto vale Yo lo único que me meto es en
that here he is claiming me the one who is claiming me if I put it I
que aquí me está reclamando a mí el queé
think that it is not a
falsa Yo pienso que no es una denuncia
false complaint I think that it is not a false complaint What is a false complaint a complaint is a false complaint okay and
falsa Qué es una denuncia falsa una
that I for example Imagine the
e que yo por ejemplo Imagínate la
lawsuit that I have filed against lerl Well that
demanda no que yo le he puesto a lerl No
I presented tweets that are
pues que yo presentara tweet que sean
false that I have made them with
falsos que los haya hecho yo con el
Paint or with
Paint o con el
Photoshop or from accounts that are
Photoshop o de cuentas que sean cuentas
parody accounts of Dallas but are not Uy from
parodias de Dallas pero no sean Uy de
Dallas but are not
Dallas de pero no sean cuentas de
lerl accounts or that I say
lerl o que yo diga
[Music] that I
[Música]
know that I basically invented it
que yo que sé que me lo invente
that I falsify things or
básicamente que falsifique cosas o sea
I mean maybe for example  Imagine that
yo a lo mejor por ejemplo Imagínate que
I file a complaint against the LERL for
yo le pongo una denuncia al lerl por
slander, okay? Well, then I
calumnias vale Bueno pues luego yo
consider that they have committed a crime
Considero que que han cometido un delito
against me, but then maybe the judge
contra mí pero luego a lo mejor el juez
says, well, no, it is not a crime, the fact
dice pues no no es delito el hecho de
that I lose does not mean that I have
que yo pierda no significa que yo he
filed a false complaint, it means that what
puesto una denuncia falsa signica que lo
I have reported is not convicted, it does not
que yo he denunciado pues no se condena
constitute a crime, it does not meet
no se constituye como delito no cumple
the requirements to be
con los requisitos para que sea
condemnable, it cannot be convicted, it cannot be
condenable no se puede condenar no se
proven, also because many times
puede probar también porque muchas veces
you report things that are
tú denuncias cosas que son la palabra de
one person's word against the other's. So if it
uno contra la del otro Entonces si no se
cannot be proven, obviously the
puede probar evidentemente prevalece la
presumption of innocence prevails. But the fact that
presunción de inocencia Pero el hecho de
a person
que una persona te
reports you and you win or the case is filed does not
denuncie y tú le ganes o archiven no
mean that the other person is a
significa que la otra persona es una
false complaint.
denuncia falsa
Now that means that I am
ahora bien eso significa que yo te estoy
imputing to you all the acts that
imputando a ti todos los actos que se
the complaint is filed,
pone la denuncia
you do not want it, that is my real opinion, my
no tú quieres es mi opinión real yo mi
real opinion, what I think is that it
opinión real lo que yo pienso es que no
is not far-fetched that you were making a
es descabellado que tú haciendo la
joke that you were taking pictures
gracia que te estabas haciendo fotos por
there and that there were people tweeting about your
allí y que había gente twitee de tus
friends, there were no people tweeting. Oops  what are you
amistades no había gente twitee Uy qué
doing in Santa Susana there are some very
haces por Santa Susana por ahí hay muy
nice houses over there no for me okay you were going to
buenas casas no para mí vale fuiste a
be the funniest of all and I think I do believe
ser el más gracioso de todo y yo creo yo
that ringing the bell I don't
sí creo que llamase al timbre yo no lo
see it as crazy look at you look at you I
veo descabellado
mean no but don't judge me
mírate O sea no pero no me juzgues a mí
think because normal people
piensa porque la gente normal la gente
good people are capable of seeing you and
de bien son capaces de que te ven y
saying let's see is it credible I no I
dicen a ver es creíble yo no yo no te
'm not accusing you of the robbery or the
estoy imputando ni el robo ni las
threats or I don't know what or I don't
amenazas ni no sé qué ni no s eso no lo
know that I don't know that's your word against his you
sé eso es la palabra tuya contra la de
understand that that justice
él me entiendes eso eso la justicia
will condemn or will not condemn me
condenará o no condenará yo
personally if it had been Dallas I
personalmente si hubiera sido Dallas yo
would have reported you for
te hubiera denunciado por
harassment I would have thrown for harassment okay
acoso yo hubiera tirado por acoso vale
Why Well because man you're already
Por qué Pues porque hombre ya estás
going to real life Then you know
yendo a la vida real Entonces ya sab
supposedly allegedly If that If
supuestamente presuntamente Si eso Si
that had happened
eso hubiera pasado
okay man were you taking pictures
vale hombre te estabas haciendo fotos
over
por
there it's that it's that it doesn't even
allí es que es que ni se me ni se me
occur to me I mean it's as if I'm in Asia
ocurre o sea es como si yo estoy en Asia
and and I start taking pictures wherever I
y y me pongo a hacerme fotos por donde
am Uploading pictures and in flat it doesn't
esté Subiendo fotos y en plana es que no
make sense the truth I mean or he
tiene sentido la verdad O sea o él lo
did it with me it doesn't make sense  It
hiciera conmigo es que no tiene sentido
would be Next Level,
sería ya Next Level
dude, it's clear he's judging me
tío sea es que claro é me está juzgando
for me Thinking, no, I'm not
por yo Pensar no yo no te estoy
accusing you, but
imputando a ti pero es que de todas
anyway, the fact that I say it's not
maneras el hecho de que yo diga que no
a
es una denuncia
false accusation, no, no, it doesn't mean that I'm going to
falsa no no no significa que yo te
accuse you of everything that the accusation says,
impute todo lo que ponga la denuncia
okay. But well, according to Laser Len, according to
vale Pero bueno según laser len según
LeR, yes, according to the SERL, according to Laser
ler len si según las serl según laser
Len, I emphasize it, eh, it's not me, eh, according to the
len Lo resalto eh No soy yo eh según las
SERL, all the accusations that are lost
serl todas las denuncias que se pierden
or filed are
o se archivan son
false. So you think it's a
falsas O sea que piensas que es una
real accusation, that is, here he just
denuncia real o sea que aquí acaba de
asserted in front of 1,454 people that he
aseverar delante de 1454 personas que él
believes that I went to Dalas's house,
cree que yo fui a casa de Dalas
threaten to kill him, and steal
amenazarle de muerte y a robarle
packages. In other words, implicitly what he
paquetes o sea implícitamente lo que
's doing here is accusing an impetus
está haciendo aquí es imput arme un
of a crime. Accusing me in front of
delito de un impe un imputar me delante
1,450 people that he thinks that I went to
1450 personas que él piensa que yo fui a
rob him. Is that okay, it's
robarle está bien está dentro de su está
within his parameters to say that, but of
dentro de sus parámetros decir eso pero
course, with a
claro con una con una es decir con una
case that is
causa que está
filed, it's ugly, obviously he can
archivada está feo obviamente lo puede
say it, he can
lo puede decir lo puede
say it, well, I can say it for something?
decir pues si lo puedo decir por algo
my son But well without
hijo mío Pero bueno sin
further ado well according to him Okay According to him they
más bueno según él Vale Según él que le
have filed the complaint okay as long as they
han archivado la denuncia vale mientras
filed the complaint the
que le hayan archivado la denuncia la
complaint is false Now if they reopen it
denuncia es falsa Ahora si la reabren
what but they have filed the
qué pero que le han archivado la
complaint if they have filed the complaint
denuncia si le han archivado la denuncia
the complaint is
la denuncia es
false and if you don't think that it is a
falsa y si tú no piensas que es una
false complaint you are imputing everything
denuncia falsa le estás imputando todo
that has been put in the complaint that I don't
lo que haya puesto en la denuncia que no
know nor everything that I don't know if it is only
sé ni todo lo que no sé si es solamente
the threats no no I don't know by heart or
las amenazas no no no s de memoria ni
everything that the things that they have
todo lo que las cosas que han
said and this has been like the icing on the cake so
dicho y esto ha sido como la guinda para
that you understand this climate a little bit
que ustedes entendáis un poco esto este
more than anything I have put it there so
clim más que nada os lo he puesto para
that you understand his attitude a little bit okay so that you do
que comprendáis un poco su actitud vale
n't judge him because I know that there
para que no lo juzguéis porque sé que
are people who are a little surprised by the
hay gente La que os extraña un poco la
attitude of this man and so on okay
actitud de este hombre y demás vale
this is a little bit so that so that you
esto es un poco para que para que lo
understand the boy okay that I am not
entendáis al muchacho vale que yo no es
because I don't want you to mess with him or
por no quiero que se metáis con él ni
anything like that okay but just
nada por el estilo vale pero solamente
so that you understand it from his
para que lo entendáis desde su
perspective
perspectiva
okay In case that I had gone I
vale En el caso de que yo hubiese ido yo
would say I went to Dallas' house to
dijera he ido a casa de Dallas
threaten him and  rob him I think there would be
amenazarle y a robarle yo creo que
more people on the internet who would applaud me
habría más gente en internet que me
than who would criticize me, I
que no que me criticaría eso lo creo en
seriously believe that eh I
serio eh yo no
am not look at the
soy fijaros la
bubble of course it is what happens
burbuja claro es que es lo que pasa
when you only have this content of
cuando Solamente tienes este contenido
course for me I reach
claro yo para mí el yo llego a
telesalseo I reach my
telesalseo yo llego a mi público del
main audience I reach such And many times
principal yo llego tal Y muchas veces
when I am going to talk about some topic Dalas I do
cuando voy a hablar de algún tema Dalas
n't know what I don't know how much I have to
no sé qué no sé cuánto le tengo que
put it in context to explain to them Who it is you
poner en contexto para explicarles Quién
know what I mean I mean
es me entiendes
today for example it is in Boca de
o sea hoy por ejemplo está en Boca de
todo el mundo and on TV we
todo el mundo y en teles también lo
have also talked about the wallet thing they say
hemos hablado lo de monedero que dicen
that one of the girls is Aime Miare's ex you
que una de las chicas es aime la ex de
have no idea ant who
miare no tienes ni idea ant de quién es
my is you
mi me
know what I mean but of course it is that in his
entiendes pero claro es que é en su
world it is this that in the case that I
mundo es esto que en el caso de que yo
had gone I said I went to Dallas's house
hubiese ido yo dijera he ido a casa de
to threaten him and rob him I think there would
Dallas a amenazarle y a robarle yo creo
be more people on the internet who would applaud me than who I would go I
que habría más gente en internet que me
seriously believe that eh And I'm not good he has said
serio eh Y no soy bueno ha dicho más
things later on I don't know why he is not in
adelante cosas no sé por qué no está en
the clicko I think it  cut badly no but he
el clicko cre lo cortado mal no pero él
says something like people
dice algo así como que la gente me
applauding me would be a hero he said or rather
aplaudir sería un héroe ha dicho o sea
look how involved he is he is simply in that
fijaron lo metio que está simplemente en
group in that group and the
el grupo ese en el grupo ese y los
public figures he
públicos que
has Well look at the logic of what he
tiene Bueno mira la lógica de lo que ha
said dal
dicho dal
veira well Javi
veira bien Javi
well Javi doxxing the name and surname
bien Javi doxeando el nombre y apellido
of láser which were not
de láser que no eran
public Bravo Javi always with your morals
públicos Bravo Javi siempre con tu moral
on the
por lo
ground what have I answered man many
suelo qué le he contestado tío muchas
times even I
veces hasta yo
myself think that the fact that you are actors that I
mismo pienso que que sois actores que os
pay you to be here is it true I
pago para para que estéis aquí es verdad
mean didn't you find what the other said scandalous
O sea no le ha parecido un escándalo lo
Eh it didn't seem
que ha dicho el otro Eh no le ha
scandalous at all what
aparecido para nada Un escándalo lo que
the other said eh No no no no what
ha dicho el otro eh No no no no lo que
seemed scandalous to you is that I
le ha aparecido un escándalo es que
put the name of a man who yesterday
ponga el nombre de un señor que ayer
put the cars on screen
puso en pantalla los
where you can see the names and
autos donde se ven los nombres y
surnames except for the licis he only crosses out
apellidos menos el del licis solo tacha
the one from the licis no no he crosses out his own
el del licis no no tacha el suyo
so I understand that he has already said it
entonces entiendo que ya lo ha dicho
many times eh And in the discussion he also
muchas veces eh Y en la tertulia también
said his name and in and when he published
lo dijo su nombre y en y cuando publicó
the complaint it was also
la denuncia también se
seen what I am telling you is the public and they are  the
vio qué os digo es el público y son los
defenders who have an audience and
defensores que tienen público y
Defenders who have each
Defensores que tienen cada
group well anyway it's okay you
grupo bueno en fin que no pasa nada tú
don't have to do a live tomorrow
no te mañana deberías hacer un directo
with Javi lerl and the day after Dallas I think
de Javi lerl y pasado de Dallas yo creo
tomorrow would be good with a live from
que mañana estaría bien un directo de
Dallas and in between a little bit of Javi in
Dallas y por medio un poco de Javi por
between a little bit of Javi Mention Jai a little bit
medio un poco de Javi Menciona un poco a
and then on Sunday since it's a day you
Jai y ya el domingo como es un día tú
know to close the week and such why do
sabes para cerrar la semanita y tal por
n't you do a little bit of dal veira Dalas
no haces un poco de dal veira Dalas
veira I was going to look at some ideas but I can't
veira iba a ver unos deas pero no
find any okay I already
encuentro vale Ya lo
have it Okay let's see
tengo Okay vamos a ver los tweets de
Dallas' tweets supporting
Dallas apoyando a
Fran Turbo's video is already crazy it's
Fran el vídeo de Turbo ya es de loco es
literally a bad one now what's
literalmente un malito ahora de qué va
Turbo's video about what's Turbo's video about
Turbo de qué va el vídeo de Turbo
my question what's paz dadi about
la pregunta mía de qué va de paz dadi de
what's Daniel Sancho or rejón for
qué va de Daniel Sancho o de rejón por
example about no no I refuse to watch
ejemplo no no yo yo me niego a ver
this I refuse to watch this
esto yo me niego a ver esto denuncia
false complaint that's it's their
falsa ya está sus
balls and that's it
[__] y ya está
laser len of showing the
laser len de enseñar los documentos del
trial documents Well that is illegal
juicio Pues que eso es ilegal el el
laser's lawyer has not committed the
abogado de láser no ha cometido la
lawyer specifically not him of course he
abogada concretamente no él claro él
oysters he goes on his channel
ostras él sale en su canal poniendo
publicly posting a a a report from the
públicamente un un un un informe del
prosecutor in a case that has not yet
fiscal en una causa que todavía no ha
reached oral trial, I don't know, so
llegado al juici oral yo no sé o sea
everyone can interpret it as they want, eh,
cada uno que interprete como quiera eh
that I'm not saying 500 to
que que yo no digo que 500 a
Nothing else says that in article 301 of the
Nada más eso lo dice el artículo 301 de
the topic they were discussing was what
la el tema que estaban discutiendo era
the lawyer said yesterday
de que era lo que decía la abogada ayer
no, let's see, that is at the discretion of the judge,
no a ver yo eso es A discreción del juez
the judge wants to get into that or it's not
que el juez se quiera meter en eso o no
worth it, I think that the judge is not going to
vale Yo yo pienso que el juez no lo va a
fine him, the truth Now if we
multar la verdad Ahora bien si nos
stick to what the article says it
ceñimos a lo que dice el artículo s
applies, let's see, he has every right
aplica a ver él tiene todo el derecho
in the world to say come out and say that it has
del mundo a decir a salir y decir que se
been archived, even to read some
la han archivado incluso a leer alguna
part or or explain the arguments,
parte o o explicar los argumentos
explain yes where the move is, it is not
explicar sí donde va la movida es que no
yet archived, that is, the
está todavía archivado o sea se pide el
archive is requested but resources are possible,
archivo pero cabe recursos
so for
entonces para
me, for me, nothing would happen to read it and
mí para mí no pasaría nada por leerlo y
explain it and all that stuff. Let's see, nothing is
explicarlo y todo el rollo ese A ver no
going to happen anyway, okay,
va a pasar nada igualmente vale
em, nothing is going to happen anyway, but
em no va a pasar nada igualmente la pero
for
para
me, no, what is not correct according to the
mí no lo que no es correcto según
article is to put it on the screen,
artículo es ponerlo en pantalla
share the  the car That's where I see
compartir el el auto Ahí es donde yo veo
the K of the question, I mean, how could he not
el K de la cuestión o sea cómo no va a
announce the file? But if
poder anunciar el archivo Pero si te lo
the press does it to you when you're a
hace la prensa cuando eres un personaje
public figure, you know constantly, but
público sabes constantemente pero al
like because, for example, the the
igual que porque por ejemplo el
the len this one was saying today that you have to
el el len este estaba diciendo hoy que
see that Pablo can't talk about the
hay que ver que Pablo no puede hablar
procedure. Of course, he can talk about the procedure, I mean, he can
del procedimiento Claro que puede hablar
talk about the procedure
del procedimiento o sea puede hablar de
of course, but how many
procedimiento por supuesto pero cuántos
lawyers aren't there on TV talking about
abogados no hay en la tele hablando de
their clients' procedures, I mean,
los procedimientos de sus clientes o sea
how many
cuántos
lawyers? How many times do
abogados Cuántas veces sal la tele los
Daniel Sancho's and Win
abogados de Daniel Sancho y de Win
Arrieta's lawyers appear on TV and everything and everything, about all the
Arrieta y de todo y de todo de todos los
events of Claro that you talk about? You talk and
sucesos de Claro que habla tú hablas y
defend your position or the position of your
defiendes tu postura o la postura de tu
client when someone is in the media,
cliente cuando alguien es mediático no
and what you can't share Pablo would be
e lo que no puedes compartir Pablo sería
information that is under
pues información que sea que esté bajo
investigation, okay, eh. That's where the issue would go, to
sumario vale eh Por ahí iría el tema a
see that they're not going to, I mean, what I think
ver que no lo van o sea yo lo que pienso
is that they're not going to fine him for two. I don't know,
es que no lo van a multar por doss no sé
the truth is, I think they're not going to fine him
la verdad yo creo que no lo van a multar
because. Well, I don't know, I think they're not going to fine him,
porque Bueno no sé yo creo que no lo van
but see, they could fine him, yes, they
a multar pero ve que podrían multar sí
could fine him. Of course, yes. I mean, if you
podrían multar Claro que sí O sea si te
touch a judge who you're messing around with, he's already fed up
toca un jue al que le estás vacilando ya
with the basils, I'll give you this, I
se harte de los basiles te pongo esta te
'll give you this fine, you understand what they usually do How many videos of How many videos of the trial, damn, my video of the trial didn't come out, something happened, I'm going to file a complaint now, on the contrary, I say damn, let them release the whole thing, you understand, the car can't be shared in principle, of course, I mean, you can
en principio claro o sea tú puedes
explain it,
explicarlo
even argue that it is what it is.
incluso argumentar que es lo que es lo
The car argues no, but if it's not
que Argumenta el auto no pero si no está
definitively archived according to the article, what
definitivamente según el artículo lo que
they're saying is that they couldn't share
diendo que no podría hacer es compartir
the screens. Now, whether it's going to
las pantallas ahora bien que vaya a
happen or not, well, I think
pasar o no pues yo creo que no va a
nothing's going to happen, but well, it might, it might, it might,
pasar nada pero bueno puede que sí puede
also, of
también
course, we all know how evil
claro todos sabemos lo malvadas que
some women can be, you give
pueden llegar a ser algunas mujeres le
them everything and everything you have and then they
das les das todo y lo que tienes y luego
try to destroy you as much as possible
buscan destruirte lo máximo posible
when you can't give them any more, I'm
cuando ya no les puedes dar más estoy
sure that even if there is some
est seguro de que incluso si hay alguna
irregularity in some license on your
irregularidad en alguna licencia de tu
part, the judge will only give you a fine and you will
parte el juez solo te pondrá una multa y
never go to jail. Well,
jamás pisará prisión alguna bueno es que
this is what we Europeans think. What
esto es lo que pensamos los europeos lo
happens is that there  apparently Well of
que pasa es que allí por lo visto Pues
course the moves are different No we have already
claro las movidas son diferentes No ya
seen that Thailand works in a
hemos visto que Tailandia funciona de
different way let's look at the same
otra manera vamos es que mira el mismo
case of Daniel well the case of Daniel
caso de Daniel bueno el caso de Daniel
Sancho was very very tough Well yes he
Sancho era mu muy tocho Bueno sí le
would have definitely received a sentence I mean yes they
hubiera caído una pena seguramente O sea
would have put him in prison
si que lo hubieran metido en la prisión
in the year like with Daniel Sancho
en el ao igual que con Daniel Sancho
but the sentence would not have been so
pero la la pena o no hubiera sido tan
severe here in Spain he would have
severa aquí en España que hubiera
escaped Well here the maximum is 25
escapado Bueno aquí el máximo son 25
years here with what Daniel
años aquí con lo que ha hecho Daniel
Sancho has done it's 25
Sancho son 25
years but well
años pero bueno
mmm we'll see what happens with
mmm veremos a ver qué es lo que pasa con
Fran I spend all day talking to
Fran yo estoy todo el día hablando con
him I hope that I hope he can
él Espero que espero que lo pueda
solve it the truth is he has
solucionar la verdad a mí me lo ha
explained everything to me well not only that he has
explicado todo bueno no solamente que me
explained everything to me but I was
lo haya explicado todo sino que yo estab
there I know the things that are there I know what aren't there I
allí sé las cosas que hay sé las que no
know everything well and and I
hay lo sé todo bien y
consider that it should not be left in
y Considero que no debería quedar en
nothing let's see if you are talking to me Now about
nada a ver si me estás hablando Ya de
issues of It's that you had to have a
temas de Es que esto había que tener un
permit to record here to record
permiso para grabar aquí para grabar
there as you are saying no that you cannot
allí como está diciendo no que no puedes
do it live no that you have to ask for a
hacer directo no que tienes que pedir un
permit to do it live I don't know no
permiso para hacer directo No sé no
true but I understand that  I hope it's not a
verad pero entiendo que ojalá no sea una
jail or anything like that okay I created
cárcel ni nada por el estilo vale Yo cre
the issue that has tarnished
el tema de que haya manchado la imagen
Yuji's image
de yuji
and let's see if you sit down If you are a
e a ver si tú te sientas Si tú eres una
person who sits on
persona que te sientas en los programas
heart programs to talk about that you have
del corazón a hablar de que tienes
problems with
problemas con las
addictions that you have a conflict
adicciones que que tienes un conflicto
with your with the father of your children about
con tu con el padre de tus hijos sobre
the issue of lands and
el tema de las tierras y
so on anyway I don't know the
demás en fin no sé la
truth let's hope that everything turns out
verdad esperemos que esperemos que salga
well man I often I trust
todo bien tío yo muchas veces Confío en
that good things happen to good people
que a la gente buena le pasa las cosas
but it doesn't always happen not always
buenas pero no siempre sucede no siempre
not always fair justice but let's see It's that
no siempre la justicia justa pero a ver
I the truth seeing everything and and and
Es que yo la verdad viéndolo todo y y y
and Knowing more than you guys Okay
y Sabiendo más que ustedes Vale
and so on for me it's [ __ ] but
y demás para mí es que una chorrada pero
well in the end it's in Criminal Procedures
bueno al final está en Procedimientos
never never never life is you know always
nunca nunca nunca es vida sabes siempre
annoying because everything you've done has
molesta porque todo lo que has hecho ha
always been with the intention of helping
sido siempre con la intención de ayudar
animals from the first moment
a los animales desde el primer momento
the work you do is exceptional and
el trabajo que haces es excepcional y
very few people are willing to give
muy poca gente está dispuesta a entregar
their lives for animals cheer up we
su vida por los animales ánimos que te
all support you then regarding this video that
todos luego respecto a este vídeo que
Fran uploaded well he answers them also
subió Fran pues da las contesta también
no after seeing it and he says there are women
no después de verlo y dice hay mujeres
that only seek to do harm
que solo buscan hacer daño
regardless of what you tell them
independientemente de lo que les digas
I wouldn't waste my time answering
yo no perdería el tiempo en responderle
anything everyone We support you it's time to fight it in
nada todos Te apoyamos toca pelearlo en
the games
los jugados
Javi but don't you think that not being able to record and at
Javi pero no crees que no poder grabar
the time the
ya la vez que fueron los policías
police went they should have told him it didn't work but well that was later It's that neither with let's see I don't know well either See if I can explain myself It's also worth it because I've talked about this many times with Trium because we have dealt with the Daniel Sancho case you already know on the
caso Daniel Sancho ya lo sabéis en el
main channel well first first we
canal principal bueno primero primero lo
had it in gossip but I took the
teníamos ent salseo pero me llevé el
subject to the main channel level that
tema para el canal principal nivel ese
case we have let's go level we are Triun
caso lo hemos vamos nivel estamos triun
and I appear in a documentary that comes out
y yo salimos en un documental que sale
now on the 27th I think it's or 29th on the
ahora el día 27 creo que es o 29 en la
platform in Paramount so Triun and I
plataforma en Paramount o sea triun y yo
participate in a documentary Well
participamos en un documental Bueno
Triun, me the lawyers the people of
triun yo los abogados la gente de
Thailand Edwin's family I don't know if
Tailandia la familia de Edwin no sé si
Daniel's family also participates
la familia de Daniel también participa
okay I mean we are very involved in the
vale o sea estamos muy metidos en el
case let's go level
caso vamos nivel han venido a nuestros
the relatives of the protagonists have come to our channels
canales los familiares de los
and we spoke with almost all the
e hablamos con casi todos los
protagonists of the story the
protagonistas de la historia los
lawyers have come not to the al
abogados han venido no a la al Canal
Our channel also, not journalists from
nuestro también no periodistas de
Thailand, that is, uh, the case, more than anything,
Tailandia o sea eh el caso más que nada
the case of Daniel Sancho, I think that
el caso de Daniel Sancho yo creo que
we have literally covered it
literalmente lo hemos cubierto nosotros
here on YouTube, mainly Trium and
aquí en YouTube principalmente trium y
I, then there are other colleagues
yo luego también hay otros compañeros
then, many of the things that we have
entonces Muchas de las cosas que hemos
learned by carrying out this case, such as, for
aprendido al llevar este caso como por
example, we also took some
ejemplo también nos llevamos algunas
things that we do not understand, not when we
cosas que no entendemos no cuando
deal with things from Mexico, things from
tratamos las cosas de México las cosas
Argentina and Venezuela and so on, it is not
de Argentina y Venezuela y demás no es
that each country works and above all each
que cada país funciona y sobre todo cada
continent in a
continente de forma
different way, in Paramont, in Paramont, we have
diferente en paramont en paramont hemos
made a documentary, well, it is from Paramont
hecho un documental bueno es de paramont
but the platform is called Sky, is that
pero la plataforma se llama Sky es que
how is the
Cómo es la
platform Sky show Sky, isn't it something like
plataforma Sky show Sky no sea algo así
a platform like Netflix and
una plataforma de estas como Netflix y
so on, let's say a very, very, very
demás vamos un documental muy muy muy
good documentary, uh, I mean, of very high
bueno eh o sea de mucha calidad de mucha
quality and very, very, very complete, very, I
calidad y muy muy muy completo muy ya os
tell you, I mean, the victim's family participates, they participate,
digo o sea participan la familia de la
well, it's in
víctima participan bueno est en
Thailand tracing everything.
Tailandia trazándolo todo
But well, what I'm getting at is that in
Pero bueno lo que voy es eso que en
Thailand things work differently,
Tailandia las cosas funcionan de otra
man, you can't go to,
tío tú no puedes ir
there are things that you cannot do
a hay cosas que tú no puedes hacer
when you go down the street, I mean, it doesn't occur to you,
cuando vas por la calle o sea a ti no se
look in Thailand, there are many
ocurre mira en Tailandia hay muchas
photographs of the King in the middle of the
fotografías del Rey en medio de la
roundabout, boom, a big photo of  King in the middle
rotonda pum foto grande del Rey en medio
or a sign with the king or flags no you
o un cartel con el rey o banderas no tú
can't be disrespectful For example, photo
no puedes faltar respeto Por ejemplo fot
taking a picture with the picture I don't know are
hacerte una foto con la foto no sé son
things that you understand that you Here you
cosas que me entiendes que tú Aquí las
see them and you say it's another it's Asia it's another
ves y dices es otra es Asia es otro
world You
mundo Me
understand me they are another culture it's another Sky
entiendes son otra cultura es otra Sky
show Time carries things from Paramon
show Time lleva las cosas de paramon
Plus here in Spain yes yes it's from Paramon
Plus aquí en España sí sí es de paramon
Plus
Plus
[Music]
[Música]
em that's what I'm telling you I mean they are in
em es lo que os digo o sea ellos son en
Thai it's
el tailandés es
very How would the
muy Cómo sería la
word be
palabra
Ah tron ​​always says it but never How
Ah tron siempre lo dice pero nunca Cómo
is the word I mean they have others they have
es la palabra o sea tienen otros tienen
another culture they have another way of
otra cultura tienen otra manera de
thinking they have another way of living
pensar tienen otra forma de vivir el
respect they have another way of living their
respeto tienen otra forma de vivir sus
beliefs their
creencias su
socializing you
sociabilizar me
understand me in Spain the king throws
entiendes en España el rey la rojan
mud at that in Thailand it's not kid
barro eso en Tailandia no s chiquillo
man Okay
hombre Vale
then things that to us may
entonces cosas que a nosotros nos
seem like nonsense in
parezcan a lo mejor una chorrada en
our culture or as such
nuestra cultura o como tal
Okay then there maybe Yes they have an
Vale pues allí a lo mejor Si tienen una
impact No no it's closed the word
repercusión No no es cerrado la palabra
is e Oh it
es
's a Oh trio always mentions it
e Ay es un Ay trio siempre lo menciona
man how angry I am he points his
tío qué coraje lo tengo la apunta la
tongue and it doesn't
lengua y no me
come out No no no it's not
sale No no no es
like things are in the culture it doesn't matter  It doesn't
como son cosas de la cultura da igual No
matter, however, then you see an
importa sin embargo luego ves a un niño
8-year-old boy driving a motorcycle, you
de 8 años conduciendo una moto me
understand, I mean, they are things that it is
entiendes o sea son cosas que es que es
another, it is another
otro es otro
continent, it is another continent
continente es ot otro continente
literally, I mean, look at it on the
literalmente o sea mirarlo en el mirarlo
map, look at it on the map, how much is
en el mapa Cuánto está
here? No, it is not strict, it is different, m
aquí No no es estricto es diferente m
eh, it is, for example, you when you are
eh es por ejemplo tú cuando tú estás
When you are explaining something Look at
Cuando tú estás explicando una cosa Mira
the same language, not the same language. Okay,
el mismo idioma no el mismo idioma Vale
when you are having a
cuando tú estás teniendo una
conversation with a person, for
conversación con una persona tú por
example, in the words that I am speaking to you,
ejemplo en las palabras que yo te estoy
eh, eh When I am talking to you, you
habl eh eh Cuando estoy hablando contigo
can interpret my words
Tú mis palabras las puedes interpretar
in various ways, they are not worth it, this is p
de varias formas ellos no vale esto es p
pan like that, out end fan, you
pan así fuera fin fan
know, solemn, no, no, that's not what
sabes solemne no no no es eso a lo que
I
me
mean, it is
refiero es
different, it is different, it is different, you
diferente es diferente es diferente me
understand me, look at the law itself, no. I mean,
entiendes mira la propia ley no O sea
many times with things about, with things about
muchas veces con cosas de e con cosas de
Daniel Sancho, we have been surprised
Daniel Sancho nos hemos sorprendido
many times when it comes to, I don't know when it comes to,
muchas veces a la hora de la no sé a la
how they handled the issue, both
hora de de cómo llevaban el tema tanto
the prosecutors and the police, you
Los Fiscales como la policía me
understand me, pragmatic, that's the word,
entiendes pragmático esa es la palabra
[ __ ]. Thank goodness someone named it
[__] Menos mal que le ha puesto alguien
pragmatic. Exactly that is the word
pragmático Exactamente esa es la palabra
that always says,
que siempre dice
trium pragmatic,
trium pragmático
yes, they are many things  man there are many
sí son son muchas cosas tío son muchas
things di Look, we often do what I
cosas di Mira nosotros muchas veces es
tell you, I mean,
lo que te digo o sea
your face and your tone of voice cause me to
ellos tu cara y tu tono de voz me causa
distrust, I really hope
una desconfianza en verdad espero que a
nothing happens to Frank Frank doesn't deserve
Frank no le pase nada Frank no se merece
so much [ __ ] with eyes your yupa
tanta caca con ojos tu yupa en ti
we trust you no but no no let's see what I
confiamos no pero no no a ver que te
cause you distrust damn what's going on But
produzco desconfianza [__] qué va Pero
if I see it as nonsense but of course it's that I do
si yo lo veo una chorrada pero claro es
n't know There in Thailand like I am
que no sé Ahí en Tailandia como yo estoy
watching Fran too
viendo a Fran también
and in some videos so worried you know
e en algunos vídeos tn preocupados sabes
man I'm worried it's that I'm
hombre a mí me preocupa es que a mí me
worried he's very stupid I'm
preocupa él es muy burro a mí me
more worried about him than himself
preocupa más él que que mismo a sí mismo
the The Movida Is that look with Daniel
la La Movida Es que mira con Daniel
Sancho for example the defense of Daniel of
Sancho por ejemplo la defensa de Daniel
course H is led by lawyers from here
claro H la dirigen los abogados de aquí
in Spain and they were like fighting for
de España y estaban como luchando por
Human Rights for the defects of
los Derechos Humanos por los defectos de
form you know I mean here the nonsense that there
forma sabes o sea aquí las tonterías que
is here in Spain that a
hay aquí en España de que se anula una
sentence is annulled because the judge has had
sentencia porque el juez ha tenido un
partial behavior or has made
comportamiento parcial o ha hecho
inappropriate comments, you're
comentarios inadecuado est me estás
telling me the Ju the judge makes himself say whatever the [ __ ]
contando el Ju el juez hace decir de lo
comes out of his dick you know I mean what you
que le sale de la [__] sabes o sea eso
're talking to me about here about
de que me estás hablando aquí de
Human Rights a guy c  dismembered
Derechos Humanos un tipo c descuartizado
note too much that we don't catch you and
nota demasiado que no te cogemos y te
cut off your ear You understand me, I mean, they are are
cortamos una oreja Me entiendes o sea
another are other things are other
son son otro son otras cosas son otras
cultures are other things and it's another
culturas son otras movidas y es otra
justice I mean no justice is not worth it no you
justicia O sea no no vale la justicia no
can't apply it's not that I know
no puedes aplicar no es que yo conozco
the justice here of no no no I mean we
la justicia de aquí de no no no O sea la
have Roman justice in
nosotros tenemos la justicia romana en
almost all of
casi toda
Europe okay They have another justice
Europa vale Ellos tienen otra justicia
we have Roman justice
nosotros tenemos la justicia romana
then we also believe in reintegration it's
luego también creemos en la reinserción
supposed to be me it's not worth it I mean well that's the That's
se supone yo no vale o sea pues esa es
the move That's my
la Esa es la movida Esa es mi
concern Maybe but let's
preocupación A lo mejor pero vamos
hope that guarantor yes yes yes yes of course I mean let's hope that let's
espero que garantista sí sí sí sí claro
hope that it remains
o sea esperemos que esperemos que quede
in what I think is
en lo que en lo que yo creo que es una
nonsense I was
chorrada
n't going to see this but look I don't give a damn about
no iba a ver esto pero mira me la suda
this let's see a little about Auron and
esto vamos a ver un poco lo de auron y
Look at the change of the change of the two
Mira el cambio de el cambio de los dos
guys from here here eh it was the same set
tío de aquí aquí eh era el mismo set
this one that this one no no things are
este que este no no están las cosas
placed like maybe no but no
colocadas como igual no pero no
no Let's see it's that Auron is also very
no A ver es que auron también está a
busy with the gym eh I mean Auron
tope con el gimnasio eh o sea el auron
is there I don't know I don't know if he  he'll notice or
está ahí no sé no sé si se le notará o
not but he's full eh he's full he's full
no pero está full eh está full está full
Let's see things
A ver vamos a ver cosillas
back you eye Juan Guarnizo right now
espalda tí ojo Juan guarnizo ahora mismo
and I'll kill him not sure no if one day I go
y lo mato no seguro no si algún día voy
to the party I want to fight against Juan
a la velada quiero pelearme contra Juan
Guarnizo I mean your dream of the party is
guarnizo o sea tu sueño de la velada es
against Juan Guarnizo he I think he's the
contra Juan guarnizo es creo que es el
only one who would accept and besides you're
único que aceptaría y aparte sois
colleagues which in part It's cool because it's
colegas que en parte Mola porque es
like eye and eh that I'm that he's another eh
como ojo y eh que yo es que es otro eh
I'm another eh this type of jackets and b
yo es otro eh este tipo de chaquetas yb
will be freaking out to put it on Of course
estará flipando con ponérsela Claro
because it's that these type of jackets
porque es que este tipo de chaquetas no
are not the clothes that I could use before
no son la ropa que podía utilizar antes
with 200
con 200
kg you need to fight with someone you hate I mean I
kg falta pegarte con alguien que odias o
know that I would put Juan to sleep and
sea yo sé que a Juan lo pongo a dormir
another one with whom I would fight but I
ya otro con el que me pelearía pero
have doubts if he would kill me
tengo dudas de si me mata
eight I don't see it so clearly there you see
ocho yo ahí no lo veo tan claro ves
Well currently you would win currently
Bueno actualmente ganarías actualmente
what I don't know how he would prepare
lo que no sé cómo se prepararía él
because he looks crazy It's that eight
porque tiene pinta de loco Es que ocho
is a psychopath Yeah of course and he crosses his
es un psicópata Ya claro y se le cruza
wire and and and and I don't know he bites my
el cable y y y y yo que sé me muerde el
neck yeah yeah  the referee goes
cuello ya sí sí que el árbitro se vuelve
crazy and stops him and such the substitution Juan let's
loco y lo para y tal el cambio Juan a
see right now He's in his prime but he's
ver ahora mismo Está en su Prime pero es
a sensitive guy Juan is sensitive yes
un chico sensible es Juan es sensible sí
that he would be afraid to hit you maybe
de que le daría cosa pegarte a lo mejor
no I think he would hit but but I think
no yo creo que pegaría pero pero creo
that I give it to him currently
que le doy actualmente
I don't Michael I think Juan would be very
yo no Michael cre que Juan sería muy
competitive eh I notice that he would
competitivo eh yo le noto que se lo
take it very seriously
tomaría muy en serio
Although both have started their
Aunque ambos han iniciado su cambio
physical change this year Ivay and Auron confirms
físico este año ivay y auron confirma
that neither will fight in the evening
que ninguno peleará en la velada
remember that last year they also
recordemos que el año pasado también
assured that the evening would not be
aseguraron que la velada no se
held at the
celebraría en el
Bernabeu next fighter of the evening
bernabeo próximo peleador de la velada
neither friends no I mean this year I'm not
tampoco amigos no O sea yo este año no
going to fight for real me neither eh him
voy a pelear de verdad yo tampoco eh él
neither and it's true I mean although well It's
tampoco y es verdad o sea aunque bien Es
true that you don't believe everything he says
cierto que todo lo que dice no te
my bad But he already looks like the
creen mala mía Pero ia se parece al
doll in the
muñeco de
back Yeah man why man
atrás Sí hombre por qué hombre
well I told you in private there are people
bueno te le dicho en privado hay gente
in there are people in the Bernabeu who Keep
en hay gente en el bernabeu que Sigue
waiting for Bad Bunny no no no no no
esperando a a Bad Bunny no no no no no
Which was the one that they were waiting for that you said
Cuál era el que esperaban que tú decías
friends I'm not lying to you He's not going to come Ah
amigos no os miento No va a venir Ah
well Yes Bad Bunny that people  He told me he's
bueno Sí Bad Bunny que la gente me decía
going to come that the people aren't going to come that
va a venir que no va a venir la gente
yes
que sí
next Auron knows all the fights
próximo auron conoce todos los combates
of the evening of the year and has assured that it
de la velada del año y ha asegurado que
will be the best edition of all there are two
será la mejor edición de todas hay dos
very
combates muy
tough fights you people don't count you anymore I must
tochos ti ya la gente no te cuenta debo
say that ibai has told me all the
decir que ibai me ha dicho todos los
fights and I think that in my opinion
combates y creo que en mi opinión de
really eh No Just because it's
verdad eh No Porque esté
here it could become the best evening
aquí puede llegar a ser la mejor velada
in terms of fights
en cuanto a combates
fights I find it incredible what he
combates Me parece increíble lo que lo
has told me Really there are two
que me ha contado De verdad hay hay dos
in particular that are
en específico
very strong that I have said yes
que muy fuertes que yo he dicho qué sí
how well and one has surprised you
cómo bueno y uno te ha sorprendido
too Of course because you didn't expect it damn
también Claro porque no te lo esperabas
being Who is that that that no be
[__] siendo Quién es que que que no que
careful be careful because if you continue around
cuidado que te cuidado que si sigues por
there they will guess No of course being
ahí lo van a adivinar No claro siendo
Who is But why Because he is not a
Quién es Pero por qué Porque no es
streamer no no it is a streamer issue but that you do
streamer no no es tema streamer pero que
not find out when everything is known you
no te enteres cuando se sabe todo
find out because it is known
enteres porque se sabe
[Music]
[Música]
everything [ __ ] [ __ ] he sent me
todo [__] [__] me mandado
okay this [ __ ] this
vale esta [__]
[ __ ] ap part It's cool because it's like there is no
[__] ap parte Mola porque es como no
need to fight with someone you hate
hace falta pegarte con alguien que odias
I know that I put Juan to
Yo sé que a Juan lo pongo a
sleep well little else no  let's see
dormir pues poco más no a ver
auron is going pretty hot and confirms
auron va bastante caliente y confirma
that he is willing to fight Juan
que está dispuesto a pelear contra Juan
guarnizo next evening the
guarnizo la siguiente velada el duom más
funniest duo on Twitch And that we all
chistoso de Twitch Y que todos echábamos
missed they comment on shokas's love situation
de menos comentan la situación amorosa
to take away the obsession he had
shokas de quitarle la obsesión que tenía
with Twitch it has been a
por Twitch ha sido una teta he sido
tit I have been good it has been total love the love that I don't know if he is in love we would have to ask him It seems like yes, I don't stop getting on tiktok I think he's in love Well he asked her he asked her to marry him in the Wow that is very
pedido matrimonio en el Wow eso es muy
romantic eh [ __ ] now from there to there
romántico eh [__] ahora de ahí a que
being a relationship and such we don't know this that
haya relación y tal no se sabe esto que
the one from tiktok
lo confirme el de tiktok
with the curly hair confirms it [ __ ] I [ __ ]
que de los pelos rizados [__] me cago
on the [ __ ] guy but listen to me But if it's already
en la [__] tío pero escúchame Pero si ya
confirmed why do they say that if it's already
confirmado por qué dicen eso si ya está
confirmed I mean the shoc and sing is
confirmado o sea lo del shoc y sing está
confirmed I was
confirmado
n't going to see this what with Win michu
no iba a ver esto lo de Win michu
hanging posters about
colgando carteles sobre
Dallas I don't know if you see it family you
Dallas no sé si venlo familia ustedes
think we'll see it or what It seems not
cre que lo veamos o qué Parece que no
but the Argos case continues my people in
pero el caso Argos continúa mi gente a
turn it seems that it is the only animal  that
su vez parece que es el único animal que
has import
tiene import
[Music]
[Música]
and host but you put me there with tina
y [__] pero me has puesto ahí con tina
me I mean you put me you combined me
me O sea me has puesto me has combinado
with tina I understand no I'm the only one who
con tina entiendo no yo soy el único que
thinks about manchita I left a record of this
piensa en manchita de esto dejé
in a space on Twitter
constancia en un espacio de Twitter
where I made a brief appearance here I
donde hice una breve aparición aquí os
leave you the compilation of my
dejo la recopilación de mis
interventions no that this is nauter this is
intervenciones no que está nauter está
nauter what do you want nauter I uploaded naut
nauter que quieres nauter subí naut
this can be
esto se me
heard let's
escucha
go Ah look it's something that I already have to
vamos Ah mira es una cosa que ya me
go now this is the last thing and I
tengo que ir ya esto lo último y se me
forgot a lot of things that I wanted to say
olvidar muchas cosas que quería decir
but no no no you have to go no no no no you have to
pero no no no te tien que ir no no no no
go No no they already wrote to me they already
te tienes que ir No no ya me escribieron
wrote to me no no no let you
escri no no no te lo dejar
go this account is not mine okay
ir esta cuenta no es la mía vale me la
they created it for me to start Yes and to continue
han creado para empezar Sí y para seguir
eh What are we talking about I'm going to see
eh De qué estamos hablando voy a ver
let's talk to the girl who is
dejemos Hablar a la chica que que está
waiting for Bel No already well here I had
esperando a a Bel No ya bueno ten tenía
several ideas in mind to say but Uy
varias ideas en mente que decir pero Uy
That one of Oh this is this Oh This girl This girl
Esa de Ay esta esta Ay Esta tía Esta tía
What was this girl I don't remember what it was that
Qué fue esta tía no me acuerdo que fue
I fought with
que me peleé con
her I mean This girl if I'm not mistaken is
ella o sea Esta tía si no me equivoco es
a bimbo who  he started to put something of
una pava que se puso a meterse algo de
my physique and and I get in and his photos almost
mi físico y y me meto y sus fotos casi
drawn of of having filter on filter on filter on
dibujadas de de de tener filtro sobre
filter on
filtro sobre filtro sobre
filter came in and destabilizing me
filtro entró y me
H messing with the voil total total total
H liando con la voil total total total
but what have I done and I haven't done anything
pero yo qué he hecho y no he hecho nada
eh There are two for one or It's all full of
eh Hay dos por un o Está todo lleno de
Venezuelans what's
venezolanos esto qué está
happening yes the complaint for me
ocurriendo sí la denuncia para mí
obviously is crazy it's crazy
obviamente es una locura es una locura
Look I mean you're going vi me du Well but the
Mira O sea tú me vas vi du Bueno pero el
trip is worth it Look at the beaches of
viaje merece la pena Mira las playas de
Dubai They are incredible Ah no of course
Dubai Son increíbles Ah no por supuesto
man of
hombre
course someone can think of spots
claro alguien puede pensar en manchitas
t fed up with already mentioning it knows
t hasta los huevos ya mencionarla sabe
where that poor
dónde está ese pobre
cat is we liaise to do a uning to be able to go
gato el liamos hacer uning para poder ir
rescue the cat you know but not what happened
a rescatar al gato sabes pero no qué pas
with the cat happens with the animalists these
con el gato pasa los animalistas estos
plastic ones is that those who are
de plástico es que los que están más
closer to Spain do not want to keep
cerca de España no se quieren quedar con
the cat
el gato
Hey hey do you think there is a lot of difference a
Oye oye cre que hay mucha diferencia un
history since you were born of all your
historial desde que naciste de todas tus
attitudes to see if you are a good person
actitudes para ver si eres buena persona
or not yes Exactly
o no s sí Exacto
esue Who has the microphone over there with
esue Quién tiene el micro por ahí con
background sound that sounds like the [ __ ]
sonido de fondo que parece el [__]
Underworld who the [ __ ] has that
Inframundo quién [__] tiene esa
[ __ ] silence yourself
[__] silénciate
[ __ ] but I have the
desgraciado pero que tengo el micrófono
normal microphone What's wrong with him, it sounds strange, it makes
normal Qué le pasa se escucha raro
noise? Ah okay the keys okay
ruido Ah vale las tecl vale
typewriter Dear [ __ ] eh We have to
máquina de escribir Dear [__] eh Hay que
do some things nter we continue
hay que hacer cositas nter seguimos
segos damn don't do anything focus here
segos ostia no hagas nada centrate aquí
but they're flirting with the girl from
pero están ligando con la chica de
Venezuela [ __ ] go somewhere else to
Venezuela cabrón iros otro lado a para
flirt So if you stop flirting it's
est ligar Entonces si paras ligar que es
a normal conversation Then your chat
una conversación normal Entonces tu chat
when we see each other [ __ ] No because I went
cuando nos veamos [__] No porque he
up I went up to ask the
subido he subido a preguntarle al
stutterer when I haven't been moral
tartaja que cuando yo no he sido moral
with you guys come on Let's go I have no
con vosotros vamos taja Dale caña va ni
[ __ ] idea I genuinely don't watch your
[__] idea yo genuinamente no veo tu
content not like you with Then
contenido no como tú con Entonces para
why are you saying that but a question that's the
qué lo dices pero una pregunta esa es la
answer that came out of the
respuesta que salió del
hole Ah okay
huego Ah vale
okay surely the one who had the accident is not
vale seguro que que tuvo el accidente no
you
eres tú
Uh
Uh
well Ah
bueno Ah
that's let's see stutterer they fooled you
esó a ver tartaja te paparon
but he didn't get offended when they made
pero él no se ofendió cuando le hicieron
jokes about the accident Of course it doesn't make
bromas del accidente Claro que no tiene
sense you have to recognize The defeat
sentido hay que reconocer La derrota
man no Ah he should admit that his thing
mano no Ah debería admitir que lo suyo
is from birth
es de nacimiento
not going to the subject wiu is hanging
no yendo al tema wiu anda colgando
Argos posters around there
carteles de Argos por ahí a la
desperately dude this is  I saw
desesperada tío esto es vi
TT I saw Twitter it seems like an outrage to me
TT vi Twitter me parece una barbaridad
man
tío
and I don't know eh To what extent I don't know what
e no sé yo eh Hasta qué punto No sé qué
measures Dallas is taking I know that I know
medidas está tomando Dallas sé que sé
that they are filing like like some
que están poniendo como como algunas
lawsuits and things like that
demandas y cosas por el estilo
eh regarding the video okay regarding the
eh referente al vídeo vale referente al
video that was uploaded there are some issues and there
vídeo que se subió hay algunos temas y
are some lawsuits and things like that
hay algunas demandas y cosas por el
okay Eh we already saw it no We were
estilo vale Eh ya lo vimos no Estuvimos
looking at something but this thing about the posters no I have
viendo algo pero esto de los carteles no
n't spoken to him about this issue The
no he hablado con el de este tema La
truth is I saw it on Twitter but it kind of
verdad lo vi en Twitter pero como que se
slipped my mind I think we haven't even
me pasó creo que ni siquiera lo hemos
discussed it here no um
comentado aquí no eem
[Music] let's
[Música]
prevent justice from handing over
evitemos que la justicia entregue el
a family's dog to an
perro de una familia a un
abuser whatever there is a
maltratador sea hay una
conviction there is a conviction eh to a guy
condena hay una condena eh a un tipo que
named Luis Pineda who also
se llama Luis Pineda que además lo lo
wins it the lawyer of these people which is
gana el abogado de esta gente que es
because the guy started to started hanging up
porque el tipo se puso
posters of the knife
a se puso a colgar carteles del de faca
The Rubén Sánchez who
El Rubén Sánchez que
also by the way has deleted the the
también que por cierto ha borrado el el
Rubén Sánchez I said it ah I don't know if I
Rubén Sánchez lo dije ah no sé si lo he
said it before about the lawyer yes I
dicho antes lo de la abogada sí lo he
said it no yes I said it Yes yes I said it that he
dicho no sí lo he dicho Sí sí lo he
deleted everything he had
dicho que borró todo lo que tenía
defending a
defendiendo a a
Marlos but what about him saying that it was the
marlos pero que de que decía que era el
same greyhound and that I couldn't tell
mismo galgo y que yo no sabía
the difference And such No but there was a
diferenciarlo Y tal No pero hubo una
conviction that he won quite rightly okay
condena que él ganó con mucha razón vale
because he was a guy who started uh
porque era un tipo que se puso a eh
hanging up posters all over Seville I
colgar carteles por todo Sevilla Me
think he hung them up at all the
parece que que los colgó en todas las
bus stops or something like
paradas de autobuses o alguna movida de
that I don't remember I don't remember well
esa no me acuerdo no me acuerdo bien
okay no what I don't remember what
vale no lo que no me acuerdo que qué
crime he was charged with I don't remember what
delito le imputaba No me acuerdo qué
crime he was charged with in I don't know if it was an issue
delito le imputaba en no sé si era tema
of keeping public money some
de quedarse con dinero público alguna
thing I don't know or being a scammer I don't know I don't
movida no sé o estafador no sé no me
remember uh I'm speaking from memory
acuerdo eh os estoy hablando de memoria
but it was
pero era
uh tremendous it was tremendous uh
eh tremendo era tremendo
and Michu grabs it and starts telling him to
eh y coge michu y y se pone a decirle a
hang up posters with a
colgar carteles con una
conversation it's just that there's no I can't find an
conversación es que no hay un no
argument for doing this I ca
encuentro un argumento ante esto hacer
n't find an argument for doing
esto no encuentro un argumento hacer
this because you still say Well
esto porque todavía tú dices Bueno
within the fight they have between
dentro de la pelea que tienen entre
them one says things to the other okay
ellos uno se dicen cosas al otro vale
but of course what are you responding to here I
pero claro aquí a qué estás respondiendo
mean dasas hasn't messed with him right now
O sea dasas no se ha metido con él ahora
no the two of them say strong things
mismo no los dos se dicen cosas fuerte
but hanging up posters around the
pero colgar carteles por la
city I don't know to what extent could give
ciudad no sé hasta qué punto podría dar
the sue this no  Of course the
las demandar esto no Claro es que ahí la
move there is that they have their fight no
movida es que ellos tienen su pelea no
but of course at this moment Dallas
pero claro en estos momentos Dallas se
was messing with him this is
estaba metiendo con él esto es
responding to
respondiendo
something I don't know for me it's very strong
algo no sé para mí es muy fuerte
Alexander but I already tell you t in a you
Alexander pero ya te digo t en un
know how it enters but you don't know how how about the
sabes cómo entra pero no sabes cómo cómo
same thing the judge takes it and says Ah
tal lo mismo coge el juez y dice Ah
well but it's that Dallas made a
bueno pero es que es que Dallas le hizo
video to Win michu in 2020 in
2020 vídeo a Win michu en el
but but I don't see that these are a
pero pero yo no lo veo que esto sean
normal response to see the mood
respuesta normalmente a ver el ánimo
retort Kendy that you are in a in a in
retor Kendy que tú estás en un en una en
a conflict with someone no but of course you do
un conflicto con alguien no pero claro
n't justify yourself or I mean for example I
no te justificas o sea por ejemplo yo me
'm fighting with someone now and I
estoy peleando con alguien ahora y le
call him pedophile and he answers me
digo pedófilo y él me responde
abuser that you hit your
maltratador qu le has pegado a tu
sister okay okay No I couldn't
hermana vale vale No yo no podría
sue why Because I just
demandar por qué Porque le acabo de
called him a pedophile before he
llamar yo pedófilo anteriormente é me
is answering me he is not doing it with the
está contestando no lo está haciendo con
intention of
Ánimo de
defaming but of course right now Dallas
difamar pero claro ahora mismo Dallas se
has messed with wismichu when was the
ha metido con wismichu le Cuándo fue la
last time Dallas said something to
última vez que Dallas le dijo algo al
wismichu he is not responding to an a  an
wismichu no está respondiendo a un a un
attack by Dallas No, in fact, there's a
ataque de de Dallas No de hecho Hay un
legal procedure that they don't talk about, I don't
procedimiento legal del que no hablan no
know why Dallas will tell it at
sé por qué el Dallas lo contará en
any moment, but well, he'll
cualquier momento pero bueno eso ya os
tell you that, but it's a complaint that they
lo dirá pero es una denuncia que le
filed against him and they
pusieron a él y
lost. But well, it seems very
perdieron Pero bueno Me parece muy
strong to me, I mean, I understand that they're
fuerte o sea entiendo que estén
desperate, eh, I understand that they're having a
desesperado eh entiendo que lo estén
bad time, in that sense, notice
pasando mal yo en ese sentido fijaros
that let's even respect each other,
que incluso respetémonos
I'm thinking of a series, But
tengo pensamiento de una serie Pero
because they're already crossing some lines
porque ya están traspasando unos líneas
and there are a few things that I didn't
y hay unas cuantas de cosas que noos
tell you, which is really bad, but well, I'll see, I'll see,
conté que que tela pero bueno Ya veré Ya
okay, but let's
veré vale pero yo
respect each other for a moment.
respetémonos momento
[Music]
[Música]
But this seems to me to be a very
Pero esto me parece t much opinión
personal opinion, eh, it seems to me. T. I mean, you're
personalísima eh Me parece T O sea estás
hanging up posters around the
colgando carteles por la
city, you're hanging up posters around the
ciudad estás colgando carteles por la
city saying that d is an abuser,
ciudad diciendo que d es un maltratador
putting up a screenshot, hey, he
poniendo una captura de pantalla heo
's hanging up Argos posters around there
anda colgando carteles de Argos por ahí
desperately, and the consequence is
a la desesperada y la consecuencia es
that d exploded because they really don't know
que d explotó por realmente no conocen
shame. Hey, a
la vergüenza Eh me llama maltratador un
guy sentenced to jail for almost finishing off
tipo condenado a cárcel por casi acabar
someone, whom he hit three bottles
con alguien a quien dio tres botellazos
in the back and split his head open, the
por la espalda y le abrió la cabeza el
joke is told.  [ __ ] no I hadn't
chiste se cuenta [__] pues no no había
seen that what the hell he had answered to
visto que que dasas había contestado a
that only as if the fact that Win
eso solo como si el hecho de que Win
michu hit a bottle had something to do
michu de botellazo tuviera algo que ver
with the treatment he gives to argo
con el trato que él le da a argo
in parallel to this frankes Of course it has to do with of
paralelamente a esto frankes Claro que
course but how could it not have to
tiene que ver claro pero cómo no va a
do with it, in other words, a person who
tener que ver o sea una una una persona
is calling another person aggressive or
que está llamando agresiva a otra o Se
is complaining about of of of some
está quejando de de de de de unas
screenshots not with
capturas de pantalla no con un
questionable behavior in those in
comportamiento cuestionable en esas en
those conversations so he is
esas conversaciones por lo que está
saying that later we will see the
diciendo que luego veremos a ver la
reality if they are true if they are not true
realidad si son verdad si no son verdad
if the acts are true or they are not true
si los actos son verdad o no son verdad
to a person who is telling you a
a una persona que te está diciendo un
guy who is condemned eh For having
tío que está condenado eh Por haberle
hit a person with three bottles Of course it
pegado tres botellas a una persona Claro
has to do with it I mean you are not here to blame
que tiene que ver O sea no estás para
the other one, this one has not stood
echarle en caran al otro no esta ha dado
up for the morons of the
la cara por los subnormales de la
discussion This is because in the talk
tertulia Esto se debe a que en la charla
that was had with him we were accused of
que se tuvo con el se nos acusó de
money laundering because of the docile treatment he
blanqueamiento por el trato dócil que se
received What's up guys I've seen that you
le dio Qué pasa chavales he visto que
're giving the people of the discussion a lot of stick
les estáis dando mucha caña a la gente
saying  that they
de la tertulia diciendo que me
were whitewashing me and and that they
estuvieron blanqueando y y que
were all quiet there and such let's
estuvieron ahí todos callados y tal a
see I want to explain something to you, I
ver Quiero explicaros una cosa yo allí
didn't go there to debate about anything at all, they
no fui a debatir de absolutamente nada
were in the discussion, I
ellos estaban en la tertulia yo lo
was listening to it and they were joking around, he'll come in, he wo
estaba escuchando y estaban con la broma
n't come in, say, come on, I'll go in to
entrará no entrará dig venga entro a
chat for a while and I came in to chat as a
charlar un rato y entré a charlar como
guest there's a very different thing
invitado hay una cosa muy diferente
when you go into a debate to debate
cuando tú entras en un debate a debatir
something or when you come in as a guest and they
algo o cuando Entras como invitado y te
ask you about anything Okay Ah I
preguntan de cualquier cosa Vale Ah yo
know that many of you are waiting that since
sé que muchos estáis esperando que como
I consider myself a friend of Dallas Ah you
yo me considero amigo de Dallas Ah
were waiting for them to give me a
estabais esperando pues que me dieran
hard time because they can't give you a hard time for being
caña por no te pueden dar caña por ser
Dallas's friend or for being
el amigo de Dallas ni por ser el amigo
whoever's friend, I mean, if a person goes up
de quien sea es decir sube una persona
to a space, they ask you things,
eh a un espacio pues te preguntan cosas
you get into an argument and you were waiting for that that you guys
te peleas y estabas esperando eso que
fight with us that they are creators of
peleáis que ellos son creadores de
gossip content when there is gossip, they
contenido de salseo cuando hay un salseo
create content but there is something
pues crean contenido pero hay una cosa
called respect and that is called
que se llama respeto y que se llama
education and that is what
educación y que es lo que utilizaron
they used that when a guest comes in, you
ellos que cuando entra un invitado le
ask them about many things, you talk about
preguntas de muchas cosas hablas de
many things And yes, we could talk about the
muchas cosas Y sí podíamos hablar del
subject of the dog  many things but but I do
tema del perro de muchas cosas pero pero
n't know why you're giving them so much
no sé por qué les estáis dando tanta
trouble if what they did was
caña si ellos lo que lo que hicieron fue
talk and we talked about many things
pues hablar y hablamos de muchas cosas
funny things personal things
cosas graciosas cosas personales
so uh you have to understand that I
entonces eh tenéis que entender que yo
didn't come up to talk about Dallas the dog
no subí para hablar de Dallas del perro
on the motorcycle and Maroto I came up uh
de la moto y de maroto Yo subí eh
simply to talk to them for
simplemente para para hablar con ellos
a while and to chat
un rato y para charlar
and
y
and you were waiting for me to start
y estabais esperando que yo me pegue con
stuttering because at a certain point
tartaja porque en un momento determinado
uh we didn't agree on something and
Eh no estábamos de acuerdo en algo y
we had a mini conflict there in a
tuvimos ahí un mini conflicto en un
live are you waiting for
directo estáis esperando que me meta
the nauter to give me a hard time because no guys they
caña el nauter porque no chicos ya me
're already giving me trouble today and yesterday and tomorrow
están metiendo caña hoy y ayer y mañana
and the next day because that's what they do I
y el día siguiente porque eso es lo que
mean they make
hacen es decir hacen un contenido de
critical content but when you go to talk to
crítica pero cuando vas a hablar con
them it's not a question of getting into a fight
ellos no es cuestión de ponerte a pelear
because it would waste time you know you don't
porque Se perdería el tiempo tú sabes no
know you say you don't say to finish I'll
sabes tú dices no dices para finalizar
leave you with an excerpt let's see Yes well let's
os dejo con un extracto a ver Sí bueno a
see but I think it's also because I
ver pero yo pienso que también es porque
had nothing to refute or rather because
no tenía nada que rebatir o sea porque
it's as if he comes here I don't know
es como si viene aquí yo que sé
mm it's as if I start refuting with
mm es como si yo me pongo a rebatir con
delox the day I went to  debate with him in
delox el día que fui a debatir con él a
the chat room you understand me and he starts
la tertulia me entiendes y se pone delox
to explain to me it's not that you see this
a explicarme no es que tú ves esta vela
green candle this green candle means that
verde esta vela verde significa que
I'm obsessed with Dallas well I'm
estoy obsesionado con Dallas pues me lo
going to believe it obviously I mean but I
voy a creer evidentemente o sea pero yo
think that if you have an
creo que si tú tienes una postura
immovable position and you go up to a person to
inamovible y subes a una persona para
chat it's that I don't know if they had
charlar es que yo no sé si ellos habían
because yes we were talking not that they
porque sí que estuvimos hablando no de
jumped on them like very much
que se les echaron como muy encima
because I didn't refute Fran I think that
porque no le rebati a Fran Yo creo que
if they jumped on them it was because in
si se les echaron encima fue porque en
their videos
sus vídeos habrán opinado diferente
some of them must have had a different opinion So yes yes if you
algunos de ellos Entonces si si si tú
have Fran on the call then you can
tienes a Fran en la llamada pues puedes
share exchange opinions with him
compartir intercambiar opiniones con él
That doesn't mean that you
Eso no significa que os faltéis el
disrespect each other or that you're mad at each other or anything like that
respeto ni que os ensar ni nada por el
but Fran Well look I mean
estilo pero no Fran Pues mira yo o sea
Fran is explaining to you that Hey look It's that
Fran te está explicando que Oye mira Es
I know about the chameleon and the
que yo sé lo del camaleón y lo del
chameleon is like this Hey look it's that I know about
camaleón es así Oye mira es que yo lo de
the dog in the cat flap well
lo del perro dentro de la gatera pues
this is the reason Hey it's that look it's that
este es el motivo Oye es que mira es que
this is the word of you know
lo de esto es la palabra de sabes
Then you say No no but  it's that I
Entonces tú dices No no pero es que yo
believe miare Because if miare says that the
me creo a miare Porque si miare dice que
chameleon thing is like that, then it is like that
lo del camaleón es así es que es así
Well there each one exposes their
Bueno ahí ya cada uno exp ponis vuestro
point No The problem is that no, they didn't
punto No El problema es que no no le
contradict him in anything or they didn't
llevaron la contrar en nada o no
know Hi grandpa and how are you I'm
supieron Hola abuelo y como están yo
half dead from the flu or cobicho
ando medio muerto de influenza o cobicho
I woke up and the first thing I see was the
me desperté y lo primero que veo fue al
cica river that I call you at the end of
cica río de que te llamo al final de
telesalseo I'm really strong XD Well I'm
telesalseo me re bien fuerte XD Pues yo
not laughing wale the truth is that I'm very
no me río wale la verdad que estoy muy
worried and also It's true that you
preocupado y también Es verdad que te
put yourself there to send me a super chat
has puesto ahí a mandarme un super chat
there no and you sent me there a lot of aco
ahí no y me has puesto ahí un monton aco
text that I don't care about from the
de texto que no me importa de la
discussion where they talk about this and a
tertulia donde se habla de esto y un
little bit of everything nauter the other day they
poquito de todo nauter el otro día me
passed me a clip of láser who was
pasaron un clip de láser que estaba
talking about the discussion and such And
hablando de la tertulia y tal Y de
suddenly they ask him Hey and what does the
repente le preguntan Oye y qué hace el
nauter do with these guys such And the
nauter con estos tíos tal Y empezó el
laser started to say like Well the truth is that I do
láser a decir como Pues yo la verdad es
n't know what nauter does with these people
que no sé qué hace nauter con esta gente
if he doesn't need to I don't understand there was
si no le hace falta No lo entiendo hubo
a comment that  they sent me eh
un comentario que me mandaron a mí eh
what did the ler lens of nauter say I don't
que dijo el ler lente de nauter no me
remember how it was but he got like
acuerdo cómo fue pero se puso así como
nauter has his things eh I don't know
nauter tiene sus cosillas eh No no sé a
what he meant by that The truth is I don't
qué se referiría con eso La verdad yo no
know what he's doing there if he'd be doing well with
sé qué hace ahí si é le iría bien ya con
his things and all and I said [ __ ] I mean
sus cosas y tal y dije [__] digo rollo
jealous girlfriend thing and he said dig I'm going to ask
novia celosa y dio dig Voy a preguntarle
my friend nauter what he thinks about it
a mi colega nauter qué opina al respecto
what the [ __ ] are you doing here what the [ __ ] are you doing here
qué [__] haces aquí qué [__] haces aquí
man in what sense do I not
tío en qué sentido no me hace
need it Not like well they told him in the
falta No en plan pues le dijeron en el
chat nauter is sick such I don't know he said
chat nauter está malito tal No sé dijo
other things that I'll tell you now and and he
otras cosas que ahora las cuento y y
started like that himself to say I don't know it's that he does
empezó como así él mismo a decir No sé
n't need to be there I don't
es que no le hace falta estar ahí yo no
understand why the guy is there if he's doing
entiendo por está ahí el tío si él le va
well with his videos he could do a
bien con sus vídeos él podría hacer
live stream and upload [ __ ] why he's there I don't know
directo y subir [__] por está ahí no sea
but whatever it has to do with you doing
pero sea que tiene que ver que te vay
well with participating in something else and that
bien con participes en otra cosa y que
you do better or what or that it's one
te vaya mejor o que o que sea una cosa
more thing that you do in your content not your
más que haces en tu contenido no tus
extracts I don't know what the
extractos Yo no sé para qué está la
chat is for and he doesn't need it as if
tertulia y no le hace falta tal como
saying I don't know for  what he gets together with
diciendo Yo no sé para qué se junta con
these guys such and such I don't know what didn't you see today
estos tíos tal no sé qué no vieron hoy
about ler today did you see today about ler to me you didn't
lo de ler hoy vieron hoy lo de ler a mí
see what l today
me lo pasaron no vieron lo de l hoy lo
about laser is criminal is in one part he
de láser es criminal está en una parte
says No but I have two theories of the
dice No pero yo tengo dos teorías de la
discussion First either they are all very stupid
tertulia Primero o son muy tontos todos
well
bien
past let's see he was not wrong or they are very
pasado a ver no se equivocó o son muy
stupid or they are very or they are only interested in
tontos o son muy o o solo les interesa
money and they have no morals
la plata y no tienen moral basado
also based on two truths
también dicho dos verdades
based but why does he say that we do
basad pero por qu él dice que nosotros
not realize that we are
no nos damos cuenta que estamos
whitewashing Dallas and we are
blanqueando a Dallas y le estamos
taking away weight from
quitando peso
the serious things that he does and I
a a las cosas graves que él hace y yo
say let's see if you want me to come here and
digo a ver yo si querés que venga acá y
I start to cry because someone says
me pongo a llorar porque alguien dice
that he hired hitmen I'm going to
que él contrató sicarios yo me voy a
laugh Until I see a hitman with
reír Yo hasta que no veo un sicario con
an AK47 shooting I have to laugh
una ak47 tirando tiro me tengo que reír
at it because if there is nothing to
de eso porque si no hay algo que me
prove it to me factually as
pruebe fácticamente como
the great Matías lamen said that fundea
decía el gran Matías lamen que fundea
San Lorenzo said it is counterfactual what
San Lorenzo que decía es contrafáctico
you say laser me if I have no
lo que vos decís láser yo si no tengo
proof you are proposing something
pruebas estás planteándome algo
counterfactual to me  I can't give my opinion, I can't
contrafáctico Yo no puedo opinar yo no
give my opinion, what do you want me to do? I come
no puedo dar qué queres quega que venga
here and say, hey Argos is not Marlos,
acá y decir eh que Argos no es marlos
for me Argos Marlos Carlos are all the
para mí Argos marlos Carlos son todo lo
same. I don't have to say anything because it
mismo yo no tengo que decir porque me
seems to me and nobody is blaming Dallas here, not even
parece y nadie blanquea a Dallas acá ni
indirectly, I've blaming him, everyone already
ni de forma indirecta lo blanque ya todo
knows who Dallas is, everyone already knows what
el mundo sabe quién es Dallas ya todo el
Dallas does. I don't know him,
mundo sabe lo que hace Dallas no sé él
for me he thinks that we have to
él para mí piensa que nosotros tenemos
go live and say, well,
que prender directo y decir bueno
boy, look what Dallas did in
muchacho eh Miren qué hizo Dallas en el
2013, this. What did he do in 2014, this. What did he
2013 esto Qué hizo en el 2014 esto Qué
do? He thinks that we should
hizo piensa que nosotros deberíamos
start all the live shows like this, what is
empezar así todos los directos lo que es
his content, what is his content,
Su contenido lo que es Su contenido
literally,
literalmente
clear and no, to me that seems sick, it
claro y no a mí eso me parece enfermizo
seems much more direct, much
a mí me parece mucho más directo mucho
funnier to me and it seems
más gracioso para mí y me parece más
healthier to go live, I watch a couple of
sano prender directos me veo un par de
Tops, a couple of videos, I react, I
Tops un par de videos reacciono me cago
laugh my ass off, that we should do that, but
de risa que que ponerme a hacer eso pero
we are stupid, we are, but Laser is
que somos tontos los somos pero láser
n't that smart either, dude, to
tampoco so tan inteligente boludo para a
me, the fact that all these people think
mí lo de que todos estos se crean que
they're all smart, all crack, and that they
son todos inteligentes todos crack Y que
all have it  very
todos la tienen
clear to me There's something that's
clarísima a mí Hay algo que me está me
starting to bother me a lot,
está me me empieza a hacer ruido mucho
Tomy from the Dance, answer you, uh, wait,
tomy de las Dance contesta tú eh espera
leave, venous guy, he hasn't answered a
dejar venoso tío no ha contestado una
question that I asked venous voso
pregunta que le hago yo al venoso voso
No, we'll give the other one the
No que ya luego le damos to al otro la
answer later, let's see why I'm
contestación a ver que por qué estoy
here, I don't know, I don't know, in fact, what am I doing
aquí No lo sé no s de hecho qué hago
[Laughter]
[Risas]
here and he
aquí y se
leaves, he leaves Hey, but I wanted you, michu, don't
va se va Oye pero yo quería te michu no
be, I'm swallowing a r here, venous No, I don't
sea me Estoy tragando aquí un r veana No
think so either, that wasn't the objective, not
tampoco creo tampoco era el objetivo no
when Fran came up Fran came up to
de cuando subiese Fran Fran subió a
chat,
charlar
no And I'll
no Y ya le
answer him. Okay, as for finishing. What can I
respondo Bueno en lo que termina Que
say before interrupting
decir antes de interrumpir tan
Tommy so horribly? Sorry, Tommy, uh,
horriblemente a Tommy Perdón Tommy eh
another factor that I think is
otro factor que yo creo que es
important is that these people don't fully
importante es que esta gente no termina
understand that Frank is a friend of Dallas
de entender que Frank es amigo de Dallas
So we're not going to
Entonces nosotros no vamos a ir a
convince Frank that you have to
convencer a Frank de que es que tienes
stop being his friend, he's not his friend, he's
que dejar de ser su amigo no es su amigo
going to defend him because that's it because he's
lo va a defender porque es eso porque es
his friend, just as we will
su amigo así como nosotros nos
defend each other for
defenderemos en entre nosotros por
some stupid thing we say because
alguna estupidez que digamos porque
we're friends and that's it. I mean, no, it doesn't
somos amigos y ya está O sea no no nos
keep us up at night, Frank  be Or stop
quita el sueño que Frank sea O deje de
being friends with Dallas if he's going to defend
ser amigo de Dallas si va a defender a
his friend then he's going to defend him and it's already
su amigo pues lo va a defender y ya
a little implicit that no, I do
un poco implícito el
n't know, don't torture him here either, no, I'm
no no sé no torturarlo aquí tampoco no
telling you a little bit of espo Ah there's nothing else Ah there's nothing else
que un poco de espo te digo Ah que no
[ __ ] dude I have to go eh I have to
[__] macho me tengo que ir eh Me tengo
go that I have [ __ ] I have one
que ir que tengo [__] me queda a mí una
night of work left today eh I mean I have to
noche de trabajo hoy eh o sea
prepare the podcast that is being
tengo tengo que preparar el podcast que
recorded tomorrow the podcast that is going to
se graba mañana el podcast que va que va
end our channels
a terminar con nuestros canales
guys Dani Estévez and Fran de la
chavales Dani Estévez y Fran de la
jungla the podcast that is going to be that
jungla el podcast que va a ser que
our channels are going to close by the
nuestros canales se cierre que por
way new tweet from
cierto nuevo tweet de
Fran What's up I just
Fran Qué pasa Me acabo de
spoke to myself I have said everything I had to
hablar he dicho todo lo que tenía que
say on the
decir sobre el
subject whatever is said they warn of
tema se diga lo que se diga advierten de
not saying anything else until
de no decir nada más hasta que termine
the process is over it could be a quick process or it
el proceso puede ser un proceso rápido o
could take quite a while thanks to
se puede alargar bastante gracias a
everyone for the support and as I always say
todos por el apoyo y como digo siempre
please leave the other party alone well that's it well that's it Well
dej por favor a la otra parte tranquila
look give me a
está pues ya está Pues mira darme un
kiss
beso
guys
chicos
guys I'm leaving Okay
chicos me voy Vale Nos
See you on Sunday see you on Sunday I do
vemos el el domingo nos vemos el domingo
n't know if not oh I want to record  a video
no sé si no ay Quiero grabar un vídeo
but I don't know if I'm going to have time I do
pero es que no sé si voy a tener tiempo
n't know if I'm going to have time I don't
es que no sé si voy a tener tiempo es
know if I'm going to have time Well in
que no sé si voy a tener tiempo Bueno de
fact I said I was going to be here for an hour
hecho dije que iba a estar aquí una hora
and I've been here for almost two I do
y llevo casi dos
n't know if I'm going to have time
em Es que no sé si voy a tener tiempo
man but I want to record a video about a
tío pero Quiero grabar un vídeo sobre un
topic that has come up in the last few
tema que ha surgido en las últimas
hours I don't know if I have time Well we'll
horas no sé si me da tiempo Bueno ya lo
see okay you guys stay tuned to
vemos vale ustedes estaros pendientes de
all the channels subscribe like and
todos los canales suscribiros like y
all that stuff rest guys
todas esas cosas que descanséis
rest guys
guapos que descanséis guapos
[Music]
[Música]